搜游子转制
(Male narrator) Love is a drug.
A class-A drug.
爱情就像吸食毒品
(Male narrator) Love is a drug.
A class-A drug.
核磁共振成像扫瞄仪显示
MRI scans have shown
that the euphoric dopamine rush
experienced by lovers
核磁共振成像扫瞄仪显示
that the euphoric dopamine rush
experienced by lovers
爱人们所经历的多巴胺愉悦的高峰期
lights up the same areas of the brain
as cocaine and morphine.
爱人们所经历的多巴胺愉悦的高峰期
lights up the same areas of the brain
as cocaine and morphine.
在大脑的同一区域就像可卡因和吗啡
lights up the same areas of the brain
as cocaine and morphine.
This reaction can act
as a powerful painkiller,
这种反应就像一支强效止痛剂
或者催产剂
and oxytocin,
known as the cuddle hormone,
或者催产剂
and oxytocin,
known as the cuddle hormone,
被称为拥抱的荷尔蒙
能使人盲目 正如情人眼里出西施
can be strong enough
to blind us to a lover's flaws.
能使人盲目 正如情人眼里出西施
can be strong enough
to blind us to a lover's flaws.
持续释放的应激激素
(Female narrator) The continued
release of the stress hormones
持续释放的应激激素
(Female narrator) The continued
release of the stress hormones
肾上腺素和皮质醇
adrenaline and cortisol
可以确保新的诱惑
can ensure that the newly-smitten
cannot eat, cannot sleep,
可以确保新的诱惑
can ensure that the newly-smitten
cannot eat, cannot sleep,
不能进食
can ensure that the newly-smitten
cannot eat, cannot sleep,
不能入睡
不能考虑其他以外的任何感情目标
and cannot think about anything other
than the target of their affection.
不能考虑其他以外的任何感情目标
and cannot think about anything other
than the target of their affection.
【情侣性爱指南】
(Man) Love can strike
anyone anywhere,
爱可以在任何人之间 任何地点发生
and often when they least expect it.
有时还会在他们最不经意的时候发生
但并非刻意发生的
But, rather than doing
what comes naturally,
但并非刻意发生的
we and the way we lead our lives
in today's busy world
在当今这个忙碌的世界
我们和我们生活的方式
we and the way we lead our lives
in today's busy world
带来了不便
put barriers in the way.
Just because nature has given us
the basic tools and instincts,
正因为大自然赋予我们基础工具和本能
It doesn't mean that
everyone is going to be great at it.
正因为大自然赋予我们基础工具和本能
It doesn't mean that
everyone is going to be great at it.
这并不意味着每个人都认为它是伟大的
It doesn't mean that
everyone is going to be great at it.
(Woman) The expectation that
we should instinctively know it all
期待我们本应该知道这一切
(Woman) The expectation that
we should instinctively know it all
can mean that we don't educate
ourselves about sex.
这可能意味着我们对性的认识还不够
can mean that we don't educate
ourselves about sex.
This increases the tendency
to dodge big relationship issues
这增加的趋势显示道奇大关系问题
This increases the tendency
to dodge big relationship issues
如安全性行为
such as safe sex, bad sex
and lack of sex.
如安全性行为
such as safe sex, bad sex
and lack of sex.
不良性行为和性冷淡
such as safe sex, bad sex
and lack of sex.
Like most things in life,
to do something well,
就像生活中大多数事情一样 做一件事情
you have to learn and practice.
你必须去学习和实践
当然性爱也不例外
And sex is no exception.
Anyone who has ever experienced
任何人都经历过
the groin-swelling, nipple-hardening
intensity of sexual chemistry,
任何人都经历过
the groin-swelling, nipple-hardening
intensity of sexual chemistry,
相互吸引的两性关系的强度
老二膨胀 乳头坚挺
the groin-swelling, nipple-hardening
intensity of sexual chemistry,
knows that when lust hits hard
都知道性欲的强烈
it overwhelms the mind as furiously
as it overpowers the body.
都知道性欲的强烈
it overwhelms the mind as furiously
as it overpowers the body.
它的强烈淹没了人的理性控制了人的身体
it overwhelms the mind as furiously
as it overpowers the body.
所以为什么性爱犹如一个强有力的驱动器
(Man) So why is sex
such a powerful drive?
所以为什么性爱犹如一个强有力的驱动器
(Man) So why is sex
such a powerful drive?
人类学家解释 逻辑上这是对繁殖的强烈需求
Anthropologists, logically enough,
put it down to the need for procreation.
人类学家解释 逻辑上这是对繁殖的强烈需求
Anthropologists, logically enough,
put it down to the need for procreation.
性爱是人类物种生存繁衍必不可少的条件
Sex is essential to the survival
of the human species,
性爱是人类物种生存繁衍必不可少的条件
Sex is essential to the survival
of the human species,
所以我们渴望得到它
so we're made to crave it.
然而我们不同于多毛的祖先
However,
unlike our hairier ancestors,
然而我们不同于多毛的祖先
it's not just about breeding.
我们不仅会繁衍后代
还会很好的做到避孕
Courtesy of contraception,
we are uniquely free
to explore the excitement of sex
还会很好的做到避孕
we are uniquely free
to explore the excitement of sex
我们是唯一自由探索性快感的物种
为我们自己
for its own sake.
(Woman) The upsides of such
freedom are obvious.
这种自由的探索显而易见
(Woman) The upsides of such
freedom are obvious.
我们可以从中认识自己
We can get to know ourselves
通过探索不同的侧面
我们与合作伙伴的性取向
by exploring different sides
of our sexuality with our partner
通过探索不同的侧面
我们与合作伙伴的性取向
or indeed different partners.
或者事实上不同的合作伙伴
我们能体验令人兴奋的欲望的高点
We can experience
the heady highs of lust
我们能体验令人兴奋的欲望的高点
We can experience
the heady highs of lust
和享受各种途径达到的高潮而不会危及妊娠
and enjoy orgasms in myriad ways
without risking pregnancy
和享受各种途径达到的高潮而不会危及妊娠
and enjoy orgasms in myriad ways
without risking pregnancy
甚至不用承担责任
or even commitment.
完美的性爱对于不同的人意味着不同的事情
(Man) Great sex means different things
to different people.
完美的性爱对于不同的人意味着不同的事情
(Man) Great sex means different things
to different people.
性欲不同 幻想不同 动机不同
Libidos vary, fantasies vary
and motivations vary.
性欲不同 幻想不同 动机不同
Libidos vary, fantasies vary
and motivations vary.
Age, upbringing, health
and personal circumstances
年龄
Age, upbringing, health
and personal circumstances
受教育程度
Age, upbringing, health
and personal circumstances
健康程度等个人情况
都会影响人的欲望
can all have an effect
on people's desires.
都会影响人的欲望
can all have an effect
on people's desires.
And an individual's preferences
can change from day to day, too.
就像个人的喜好也会每天改变
And an individual's preferences
can change from day to day, too.
在某些情况下
On some occasions, tender kisses
and slow sensual caresses
在某些情况下
On some occasions, tender kisses
and slow sensual caresses
温柔的吻和感官缓慢地爱抚
可能会带来前所未有的激情
might bring passion to the fore.
(Woman) Sex can be about lust or love,
性爱包括性欲和爱情
诱惑或庆典
temptation or celebration,
一个下雨的星期天感情或者干脆支配自己
affection or simply occupying
yourselves on a rainy Sunday.
一个下雨的星期天感情或者干脆支配自己
affection or simply occupying
yourselves on a rainy Sunday.
没有人会保证完美的性爱
No one motivation
will guarantee great sex,
没有人会保证完美的性爱
No one motivation
will guarantee great sex,
但它确实值得探讨所有可选物
but it's certainly worth exploring
all the options.
但它确实值得探讨所有可选物
but it's certainly worth exploring
all the options.
它的那些感到舒服的人
It's those people
who feel comfortable
它的那些感到舒服的人
enjoying, understanding
and exploring sex
它的那些感到舒服的人
enjoying, understanding
and exploring sex
享受
enjoying, understanding
and exploring sex
认识和探索性
倾向于把脱掉衣服作为最大乐趣
that tend to have the most fun
with their clothes off.
倾向于把脱掉衣服作为最大乐趣
that tend to have the most fun
with their clothes off.
(Man) Being honest
about your own cravings
要真诚的表达自己的欲望
(Man) Being honest
about your own cravings
愿意探索你爱人的每一寸肌肤
and willing to explore
every inch of your lover's body
愿意探索你爱人的每一寸肌肤
为了在学习中更好地引导他们
in a bid to learn
what really turns them on
为了在学习中更好地引导他们
is an essential part of great sex.
这是完美性爱必不可少的一部分
毕竟不能为了满足自己的性欲而去做爱
(Woman) Sex, after all,
can't just be about your desires.
毕竟不能为了满足自己的性欲而去做爱
(Woman) Sex, after all,
can't just be about your desires.
要获得真正的激情它必须是我们自己的倾向
To be really synapse-sparking,
it has to be about tending to your own
要获得真正的激情它必须是我们自己的倾向
伴侣的个人欲望想要得到什么需要什么
and your partner's individual
desires, wants and needs,
伴侣的个人欲望想要得到什么需要什么
and your partner's individual
desires, wants and needs,
找到这些条件的交集点
and finding the glorious intersections
between those points.
找到这些条件的交集点
and finding the glorious intersections
between those points.
调情是男人为了交配而进行的仪式
(Man) Flirting is man's mating ritual.
It's the first way we indicate desire,
这是我们第一种表明愿望的方式
大多数都是围绕它产生的
and a host of industries
are built up around it,
大多数都是围绕它产生的
and a host of industries
are built up around it,
从速配到更多的传统单身去俱乐部酒吧
from speed-dating to more traditional
singles' nights, pubs to clubs.
从速配到更多的传统单身去俱乐部酒吧
from speed-dating to more traditional
singles' nights, pubs to clubs.
A plethora of social occasions
are little more
过量的社交场合是多于
than thinly-disguised
seduction opportunities.
过量的社交场合是多于
than thinly-disguised
seduction opportunities.
变相诱惑的机会
than thinly-disguised
seduction opportunities.
许多人开始抱怨夜总会生活变得乏昧
(Woman) Many people complain
that nightclubs become duller
许多人开始抱怨夜总会生活变得乏昧
once you stop being single.
一旦你告别单身
这正好说明了他们是如此认真地设计过
Which just goes to show
how carefully they are designed
这正好说明了他们是如此认真地设计过
to help find a mate.
为了他们可以找到一个伴侣
虽然你可能并不一定会
获得一个良好的对话机会
And while you may not necessarily
get a chance for a good conversation,
虽然你可能并不一定会
获得一个良好的对话机会
You certainly get a good opportunity
to scope out potential conquests.
但你可以发现其他能打动对方的好机会
You certainly get a good opportunity
to scope out potential conquests.
调情给出了一个微妙感兴趣的迹象
(Man) Flirting gives a subtle
indication of interest -
调情给出了一个微妙感兴趣的迹象
(Man) Flirting gives a subtle
indication of interest -
suggesting you are up
for forming a deeper connection,
建议您形成更深的联系
but without the risk that comes
with a more direct approach.
但这没有风险 可以更直接的方式来
but without the risk that comes
with a more direct approach.
就像直接的眼神接触和开口笑
(Woman) Things like direct eye contact
and an open smile
就像直接的眼神接触和开口笑
(Woman) Things like direct eye contact
and an open smile
可以采取行动来表明欲望和建议的吸引力
can act to indicate desire
and suggest attraction.
可以采取行动来表明欲望和建议的吸引力
(Man) Although some people
are innately flirtatious,
虽然有些人天生娇媚
it's also a skill that can be
learned and developed.
虽然有些人天生娇媚
it's also a skill that can be
learned and developed.
但这也是一个可以学习和发展的技能
it's also a skill that can be
learned and developed.
练习调情有助于克服缺乏自信
(Woman) Practicing flirting helps
overcome lack of self-confidence
练习调情有助于克服缺乏自信
(Woman) Practicing flirting helps
overcome lack of self-confidence
和被拒绝时的恐惧
and the fear of rejection.
其主要目标是要激发你对目标的想象
The main goal is to spark
the imagination of your target.
其主要目标是要激发你对目标的想象
The main goal is to spark
the imagination of your target.
关键的一点要记住 当你试图挑逗
(Man) One key thing to keep in mind
when you're attempting to flirt
关键的一点要记住 当你试图挑逗
is your body language.
运用你的身体语言
虽然你不希望完全侵入他人的个人空间
Although you don't want to completely
invade someone's personal space,
虽然你不希望完全侵入他人的个人空间
只要有一点侵犯就发送信号
a bit of encroachment
sends the signal
只要有一点侵犯就发送信号
有更重要的不仅仅是要在这里聊天
that there's more than just
chatting going on here.
有更重要的不仅仅是要在这里聊天
that there's more than just
chatting going on here.
热情的微笑 用手来一个随意的触摸
(Woman) A welcoming smile,
a casual touch of the hand,
热情的微笑 用手来一个随意的触摸
或者认真的听别人倾诉
or simply listening
to someone attentively
或者认真的听别人倾诉
都将有助于暗示出你的吸引力
will all help indicate your attraction,
虽然一些人更喜欢公开的方式
though some prefer
the more overt approach.
虽然一些人更喜欢公开的方式
though some prefer
the more overt approach.
(Man) Leaning towards someone,
有人倾向于
通常需要在嘈杂的环境
which is often necessary
in a noisy environment,
通常需要在嘈杂的环境
which is often necessary
in a noisy environment,
它是另一种方式来显示你的兴趣
is another way to show your interest.
你看起来更自信 你就会显得更有吸引力
The more confident you look,
the more attractive you'll seem.
你看起来更自信 你就会显得更有吸引力
The more confident you look,
the more attractive you'll seem.
(Woman) By relaxing, enjoying yourself,
and using those signals skilfully,
通过放松享受自己 巧妙地利用这些信号
您可以建立是否有一个有潜在伴侣的连接
you can establish whether there's
a connection with a potential mate,
您可以建立是否有一个有潜在伴侣的连接
如果有 谁知道它可能会导致什么结果
and, if there is,
who knows where it could lead?
如果有 谁知道它可能会导致什么结果
and, if there is,
who knows where it could lead?
性爱是人类必需的一个核心
(Man) Sex is a core human need,
如同呼吸 睡眠和饮食一样自然
as natural as breathing,
sleeping and eating.
如同呼吸 睡眠和饮食一样自然
And, as with all these needs,
与所有这些需求
the hunger for sex can be
a strong motivating force.
对性的饥渴可以成为一个强大的原动力
the hunger for sex can be
a strong motivating force.
我们渴望点燃身体对性的欲望
Our bodies ignite the desire for sex,
一旦有强烈的欲望
and once the craving is there,
这是达到快乐的第一步 能使得更加亲密
it's the first step towards the joys
that intimacy can bring.
这是达到快乐的第一步 能使得更加亲密
it's the first step towards the joys
that intimacy can bring.
(Woman) Physical attraction
is an essential part of desire.
身体的吸引力是欲望的重要组成部分
(Woman) Physical attraction
is an essential part of desire.
有时候只是看到强壮的肌肉
Sometimes, just the sight
of a muscular pair of arms
有时候只是看到强壮的肌肉
or a hint of cleavage can activate
a person's sex hormones,
或者乳沟就可以激活一个人的性激素
or a hint of cleavage can activate
a person's sex hormones,
然后振奋身心付诸于行动
which then rouse the body and mind
into action.
然后振奋身心付诸于行动
which then rouse the body and mind
into action.
最棘手的事情是满足欲望
(Man) The trickiest thing
about fulfilling desires
最棘手的事情是满足欲望
能够找到那个与你在性之间合拍的人
can be finding the person
who really clicks with you sexually.
能够找到那个与你在性之间合拍的人
can be finding the person
who really clicks with you sexually.
(Woman) We're genetically
hotwired to be drawn to partners
我们绘制出伴侣在遗传方面的热边线
来确保他是优良的育种
who seem to be good
breeding stock.
来确保他是优良的育种
who seem to be good
breeding stock.
年轻 健康 力量是大众的青睐
Youth, health and strength
are universally appealing.
年轻 健康 力量是大众的青睐
Youth, health and strength
are universally appealing.
但比这更重要的是
But more than that,
我们也吸引了人们信息素的示意
we're also attracted to people
whose pheromones indicate
我们也吸引了人们信息素的示意
we're also attracted to people
whose pheromones indicate
他们有一个自己的互补性免疫系统
they have a complementary
immune system to our own.
他们有一个自己的互补性免疫系统
they have a complementary
immune system to our own.
当我们遇到一个适合的
When we meet a match,
大脑就会释放出的复杂的混合化学物质
the brain releases a complex
cocktail of chemicals
大脑就会释放出的复杂的混合化学物质
the brain releases a complex
cocktail of chemicals
它们能够产生一种兴奋和幸福
that produce a rush
of excitement and well being,
它们能够产生一种兴奋和幸福
让我们与爱人私在一起 使我们感到充实
bonding us to a lover
and making us feel content.
让我们与爱人私在一起 使我们感到充实
bonding us to a lover
and making us feel content.
身体会共同增加这些化学物质
(Man) The body conspires
to enhance these chemicals.
身体会共同增加这些化学物质
The pupils dilate, making us
look more attractive to a partner.
身体会共同增加这些化学物质
The pupils dilate, making us
look more attractive to a partner.
随着学生群体的增加
The pupils dilate, making us
look more attractive to a partner.
让我们看到了一个更具吸引力的性伴侣
The pupils dilate, making us
look more attractive to a partner.
Meanwhile, the blood makes
a bee-line to parts of the body
与此同时
Meanwhile, the blood makes
a bee-line to parts of the body
血液会以最短的距离输送到身体各部分
来公开示意欲望
that openly indicate desire.
导致外部的迹像有乳头坚挺和阴茎勃起
Resulting in external signs such
as erect nipples and a hardening penis,
导致外部的迹像有乳头坚挺和阴茎勃起
这些都有助于激发他们的性伴侣
如果碰巧瞥了一眼
which all serve to arouse a partner
if they happen to catch a glimpse,
这些都有助于激发他们的性伴侣
如果碰巧瞥了一眼
which all serve to arouse a partner
if they happen to catch a glimpse,
即使通过我们的衣服
even through our clothes.
(Woman) While research has shown
that 90% of long-term couples
研究表明90％结婚很久的夫妇
feel they are with the right partner,
自己感觉他们与性伴侣的生活很好
但超过50％的婚姻最终以离婚结束
over 50% of marriages
end in divorce.
但超过50％的婚姻最终以离婚结束
over 50% of marriages
end in divorce.
强烈的身体吸引力和美好的性爱是可以发展的
Still, strong physical attraction
and great sex can develop
强烈的身体吸引力和美好的性爱是可以发展的
假如夫妇用足够的能量和热情
来维持他们的亲密生活
provided the couple bring enough energy
and enthusiasm to their intimate lives-.
假如夫妇用足够的能量和热情
来维持他们的亲密生活
provided the couple bring enough energy
and enthusiasm to their intimate lives-.
一旦有了欲望的感觉
(Man) Once the feeling
of desire kicks in,
一旦有了欲望的感觉
we use the same kinds of seduction
techniques found in the animal kingdom.
一旦有了欲望的感觉
we use the same kinds of seduction
techniques found in the animal kingdom.
我们和动物王国的其他物种一样
运用同样的诱惑技巧
we use the same kinds of seduction
techniques found in the animal kingdom.
例如鸟类梳理毛发 整理羽毛
Grooming, preening, teasing
and sometimes territorial behavior.
例如鸟类梳理毛发 整理羽毛
Grooming, preening, teasing
and sometimes territorial behavior.
挑逗和争夺领地的行为
Grooming, preening, teasing
and sometimes territorial behavior.
在公众场合简单的把手放在爱人的手臂上
Simply placing a hand
on a lover's arm in public
在公众场合简单的把手放在爱人的手臂上
Simply placing a hand
on a lover's arm in public
就能暗示他们没戏了
can indicate to others
that they are taken,
就能暗示他们没戏了
can indicate to others
that they are taken,
在公众场合接吻可以明显地
向他人暗示没希望了
and kissing in public is a clear indication
to others to keep their hands off.
在公众场合接吻可以明显地
向他人暗示没希望了
(Woman) Sadly, these feelings
don't always last.
可悲的是这些感觉并不总是在最后
(Woman) Sadly, these feelings
don't always last.
最有吸引力的化学物质
The most powerful chemicals
of attraction
最有吸引力的化学物质
only last for around three months,
仅能持续3个月
在一年半的时间内慢慢消退
with almost all of them fading away
within 18 months.
在一年半的时间内慢慢消退
with almost all of them fading away
within 18 months.
这就是为什么许多夫妻
可能会觉得那种神奇已消退
This is why many couples may feel
the magic has faded.
这就是为什么许多夫妻
可能会觉得那种神奇已消退
This is why many couples may feel
the magic has faded.
(Man) They identify the feeling of love
as being the heady mix of chemicals,
他们确定这是因为令人兴奋的感觉
源于混合化学物质
(Man) They identify the feeling of love
as being the heady mix of chemicals,
这就是为什么它如此重要
而非仅仅是发生性关系
which is why it's so important to develop
more than merely a sexual relationship
这就是为什么它如此重要
而非仅仅是发生性关系
when you first meet a lover.
这就是为什么它如此重要
而非仅仅是发生性关系
when you first meet a lover.
当你第一次遇到一个情人
But, with continued effort,
加上持续的努力
there's no reason that
a long-term loving relationship
加上持续的努力
there's no reason that
a long-term loving relationship
我们没有理由认为一个长期的恋爱关系
there's no reason that
a long-term loving relationship
更不要奢望性爱
shouldn't result in even better sex
在初期阶段超过化学高点
than the chemical-driven highs
of the early days.
在初期阶段超过化学高点
than the chemical-driven highs
of the early days.
(Woman) It's only when we kiss
只有当我们亲吻时
that chemistry really has
the chance to work its magic.
这些化学物质才有机会显示它的神奇
that chemistry really has
the chance to work its magic.
有了适当的性伴侣世界就显得渺小了
With the right partner, the world
shrinks down into nothing but the point
有了适当的性伴侣世界就显得渺小了
当你的嘴唇吻到到你的爱人时
at which your lips are making
contact with your lover's.
当你的嘴唇吻到到你的爱人时
at which your lips are making
contact with your lover's.
随着吻得深入血液都充到我们的嘴唇上
As the kiss deepens,
the blood rushes into your lips,
随着吻得深入血液都充到我们的嘴唇上
indicating your desire,
increasing sensitivity
暗示欲望 增加敏感度
indicating your desire,
increasing sensitivity
唤醒他们的欲望
and making them firm with arousal.
刚开始接吻时都充满了激情
(Man) That first kiss can
be thick with passion.
刚开始接吻时都充满了激情
(Man) That first kiss can
be thick with passion.
尽管这可以诱惑我们进行深入的舌吻
While it can be tempting
to dive in tongue first,
尽管这可以诱惑我们进行深入的舌吻
While it can be tempting
to dive in tongue first,
整个体验会变得很诱人
the entire experience becomes
so much more enticing
整个体验会变得很诱人
如果你循循渐进的话
if you take a softly-softly approach.
进行深情的对望
(Woman) Looking into
each other's eyes
进行深情的对望
as you breathe
each other's breath,
进行深情的对望
as you breathe
each other's breath,
可以感觉到彼此的呼吸
as you breathe
each other's breath,
等待着对方的下一步
each waiting for the other
to make the first move,
等待着对方的下一步
each waiting for the other
to make the first move,
这可以营造出最令人陶醉的时刻之一
在彼此迅速发展的关系中
can create one of the most intoxicating
moments of a burgeoning relationship.
这可以营造出最令人陶醉的时刻之一
在彼此迅速发展的关系中
can create one of the most intoxicating
moments of a burgeoning relationship.
(Man) Going in too hard and fast
to start with
开始就蛮干的话
can indicate inexperience or a lack
of concern for your partner's enjoyment.
开始就蛮干的话
can indicate inexperience or a lack
of concern for your partner's enjoyment.
就会显得你缺乏经验或不关心你伴侣的享受
can indicate inexperience or a lack
of concern for your partner's enjoyment.
好的东西是需要时间等待
Good things come to those who wait,
and never is this truer
than with kissing.
从来没有比这更真实的接吻
and never is this truer
than with kissing.
While wet kisses do have their place,
虽然舌吻的确有自已位置
但过于猛烈
an overactive, probing tongue suggests
you want to rush to the finishing line
但过于猛烈
an overactive, probing tongue suggests
you want to rush to the finishing line
会给人感觉就舌头好像很着急
rather than enjoying the sensual
pleasures that a kiss has to offer.
而不是享受一个吻所给予的肉体上的快乐
rather than enjoying the sensual
pleasures that a kiss has to offer.
当接吻的时候缺乏激情
这会阻碍关系的更近一步发展
(Woman) Many a relationship has been
thwarted by a lack-lustre first kiss.
当接吻的时候缺乏激情
这会阻碍关系的更近一步发展
(Woman) Many a relationship has been
thwarted by a lack-lustre first kiss.
尽管技巧由一个能发挥作用
While technical skill has a part to play,
如果当第一次见到你的嘴唇
却没有那神奇的尖啸声时
if there isn't that magical zing
when your lips first meet,
如果当第一次见到你的嘴唇
却没有那神奇的尖啸声时
if there isn't that magical zing
when your lips first meet,
它暗示可能这没有足够的身体协调性
it can indicate there may not be
enough physical compatibility
它暗示可能这没有足够的身体协调性
for passion to grow.
由于激情的增加
舔下你的嘴唇 当你的嘴离得很近时
(Man) Licking your own lips when
your mouth is mere millimeters away
舔下你的嘴唇 当你的嘴离得很近时
from the object of your affections
寄予你的感情
表达一个淫荡的挑逗
这会使他们渴望与你接吻
delivers a sensual tease that will make
them yearn to press their lips to yours.
表达一个淫荡的挑逗
这会使他们渴望与你接吻
delivers a sensual tease that will make
them yearn to press their lips to yours.
And taking that first kiss slowly,
刚开始吻要慢慢的进行
好让你的嘴唇微妙碰触你的爱侣
letting your lips delicately
touch your lover's
好让你的嘴唇微妙碰触你的爱侣
在延长挑逗之前
before pulling away
to extend the tease
在延长挑逗之前
before pulling away
to extend the tease
这将有助于点燃我们的欲望
will serve to make the stomach flip
and the heart race.
这将有助于点燃我们的欲望
will serve to make the stomach flip
and the heart race.
(Woman) By teasing and withdrawing,
deepening the kiss then pulling away,
通过时不时的挑逗 长吻彼此
(Woman) By teasing and withdrawing,
deepening the kiss then pulling away,
你能促进营造缓慢的激情诱惑
you help to build the passion
slowly and seductively
你能促进营造缓慢的激情诱惑
you help to build the passion
slowly and seductively
关于你的欲望毫无疑问
while still leaving your lover
in no doubt as to your desires.
关于你的欲望毫无疑问
while still leaving your lover
in no doubt as to your desires.
(Man) That said,
as your relationship progresses,
这就是说当你们的关系进一步发展
(Man) That said,
as your relationship progresses,
更深层的发展 热吻是一种
令人陶醉的方式向你的爱侣展示
deep, hard kissing can be
an intoxicating way to show your lover
更深层的发展 热吻是一种
令人陶醉的方式向你的爱侣展示
that you still desire them
as much as you did
更深层的发展 热吻是一种
令人陶醉的方式向你的爱侣展示
that you still desire them
as much as you did
她还希望你吻得更久
在你们关系的初期
in the early days
of your relationship.
在你们关系的初期
in the early days
of your relationship.
热吻是猛烈的
A passionate kiss
can be achingly intense.
热吻是猛烈的
被点燃的欲望可以让你的嘴唇吻遍爱侣的脸
Fueling the desire to let your lips
explore your partner's face,
被点燃的欲望可以让你的嘴唇吻遍爱侣的脸
脖子
neck, shoulders and beyond.
香肩等等
这会使你全身燥热
It will make your skin tingle
and blood pound,
这会使你全身燥热
It will make your skin tingle
and blood pound,
让你的爱侣充满期待
and leave your lover
filled with anticipation.
让你的爱侣充满期待
and leave your lover
filled with anticipation.
(Woman) And kissing isn't just
about the lips.
接吻并不是只吻嘴唇
Leisurely exploring your lover's neck,
earlobes and shoulders
慢慢地探索你的爱人的脖子
Leisurely exploring your lover's neck,
earlobes and shoulders
耳垂和香肩
Leisurely exploring your lover's neck,
earlobes and shoulders
can be achingly sensual.
会激发她的性欲
Many women list their neck as one of
their most sensitive erogenous zones,
许多女性的脖子都被列为最敏感的性感带
Many women list their neck as one of
their most sensitive erogenous zones,
精巧的脖子亲吻是更多前戏的开始
with delicate neck kissing
acting as more of a turn-on
精巧的脖子亲吻是更多前戏的开始
than a more obvious approach
of caressing the breasts.
比爱抚乳房更有效
than a more obvious approach
of caressing the breasts.
(Man) While love bites are best
avoided after adolescence,
尽管在青春期之后 爱痕是最好避免的
(Man) While love bites are best
avoided after adolescence,
温柔地咬和挑逗的吮吸可以发送期待
gently nibbling and teasing suction
can send shivers of anticipation
温柔地咬和挑逗的吮吸可以发送期待
through your lover's body.
传遍爱侣的身体
接吻是会上瘾的
(Woman) Kissing is addictive.
它会在爱侣之间形成强劲持久的纽带
It forms a strong, lasting bond
between you and your partner.
它会在爱侣之间形成强劲持久的纽带
It forms a strong, lasting bond
between you and your partner.
这是一个众所周知的 当关系破裂时
It's a well-known truth that
when relationships break down,
这是一个众所周知的 当关系破裂时
It's a well-known truth that
when relationships break down,
it's usually the first kissing
that stops even before sex.
这是正常的接吻能阻止发生性关系
it's usually the first kissing
that stops even before sex.
接吻可以让他人看到你是多么的好相处
Think of kissing as the litmus test
of how well you're getting along.
接吻可以让他人看到你是多么的好相处
Think of kissing as the litmus test
of how well you're getting along.
嘴唇上布满了神经元
(Man) The lips are densely
populated with nerves.
嘴唇上布满了神经元
激烈的热吻确保这些神经元
An intense session of kissing ensures
those nerves,
激烈的热吻确保这些神经元
combined with those on the tongue
and in the mouth,
激烈的热吻确保这些神经元
combined with those on the tongue
and in the mouth,
与在舌头上 嘴里的神经元结合
constantly send messages
to the brain.
不断地向大脑发送消息
constantly send messages
to the brain.
This helps unleash numerous
sexy chemicals
这有助于释放许多性感的化学物质
能使你感到放松唤醒你的伴侣
that make you feel relaxed, aroused,
connected to a partner,
能使你感到放松唤醒你的伴侣
that make you feel relaxed, aroused,
connected to a partner,
为达到下一个阶段做准备
and ready to take things
to the next level.
为达到下一个阶段做准备
and ready to take things
to the next level.
(Woman) People stay in love
when they feel valued,
人们依然相爱当他们还彼此重视对方
adored and appreciated sexually.
喜欢欣赏彼此的性
Don't be complacent.
不要自鸣得意
让你的伴侣觉得性感
Keep making your partner feel sexy,
keep flirting,
and don't let the kissing stop.
继续调情不要让吻停下来
keep flirting,
and don't let the kissing stop.
你永远不知道它会向何处发展
You never know where it might lead.
(Man) Touch is one of our most
basic communication methods.
爱抚是我们最基本的交流方式之一
(Man) Touch is one of our most
basic communication methods.
However, only the caress of a lover
has the ability
然而只有彼此爱抚有能力
However, only the caress of a lover
has the ability
点燃你们的激情
to set your nerves alight
探索无限的可能性
and make your mind explore
the infinite possibilities
探索无限的可能性
and make your mind explore
the infinite possibilities
彼此赤裸的享受着幸福时刻
contained within than blissful moment
when skin meets skin.
彼此赤裸的享受着幸福时刻
contained within than blissful moment
when skin meets skin.
(Woman) Even something as simple
as your fingertips meeting your lover's
即使有一些很简单
用你的指尖就可以满足你的爱人
(Woman) Even something as simple
as your fingertips meeting your lover's
性爱的承诺
can be charged with erotic promise.
(Man) The average human has
an impressive two square metres
人类平均有两平方米的令人印象深刻的
of skin surface area.
皮肤表面面积
这使得皮肤上有数百万的神经末梢
That makes the skin,
packed with millions of nerve endings,
这使得皮肤上有数百万的神经末梢
your body's largest erogenous zone.
是身体上最爽的性感带
All it takes to activate it
is a touch from the right person.
正确的爱抚都可以唤醒欲望
All it takes to activate it
is a touch from the right person.
相互爱抚有助手唤起彼此的欲望
(Woman) Stroking each other helps you
rouse each other's desires,
相互爱抚有助手唤起彼此的欲望
(Woman) Stroking each other helps you
rouse each other's desires,
getting the juices flowing,
and making you both eager for more.
体液分泌 欲火焚身
getting the juices flowing,
and making you both eager for more.
(Man) Caressing your partner's body
teaches you its landscape.
爱抚对方的身体要像欣赏艺品
(Man) Caressing your partner's body
teaches you its landscape.
It's only by exploring
that you can discover exactly
这只是通过探索你就可以准确地发现
什么可以让你的爱人淫声连连
what makes your lover tick.
Although the breasts and genitals
are the obvious erogenous zones,
虽然乳房和生殖器是显而易见的性敏感区
Although the breasts and genitals
are the obvious erogenous zones,
By allowing your hands
to roam more thoroughly,
但是手可以更彻底地漫游
By allowing your hands
to roam more thoroughly,
你可以发现你的爱人独特的身体曲线
you can discover your lover's
unique body blueprint.
你可以发现你的爱人独特的身体曲线
you can discover your lover's
unique body blueprint.
(Woman) For some, a finger traced
along the spine,
对于这些手指沿脊柱蔓延
back of the knee
or the nape of the neck,
到膝盖后面或者脖子的后颈
back of the knee
or the nape of the neck,
比X级电影能产生更多的强烈色情
can produce a strong and erotic charge
as more X-rated exploration.
比X级电影能产生更多的强烈色情
can produce a strong and erotic charge
as more X-rated exploration.
对于其他人
For others, delicate kisses
to the buttocks, inner ankle or toes
对于其他人
For others, delicate kisses
to the buttocks, inner ankle or toes
细腻的亲吻屁股 内脚踩或者脚趾
For others, delicate kisses
to the buttocks, inner ankle or toes
是幸福的关键
are the key to sexual bliss.
There's no right or wrong,
simply what your lover likes best.
没有对与错
There's no right or wrong,
simply what your lover likes best.
只是你的爱人最喜欢哪一种
There's no right or wrong,
simply what your lover likes best.
(Man) As with most sexual contact,
正如大多数的性接触
caressing a lover builds
a feeling of intimacy
爱抚情人是为了更加亲密
and releases the cuddle
hormone oxytocin.
还可以释放拥抱的荷尔蒙
and releases the cuddle
hormone oxytocin.
这使你更容易接受爱抚和被抚摸
This makes you more receptive
to touching and being touched,
这使你更容易接受爱抚和被抚摸
This makes you more receptive
to touching and being touched,
当你放松并达到兴奋时就会发送信号
sending the signal that
you can relax into your arousal.
当你放松并达到兴奋时就会发送信号
sending the signal that
you can relax into your arousal.
营造这些慢吻的感觉 对视和挑逗
Building these feelings with slow kisses,
tender eye gazing and teasing strokes
营造这些慢吻的感觉 对视和挑逗
这只会提高预期
will only serve to heighten
the anticipation.
这只会提高预期
will only serve to heighten
the anticipation.
(Woman) Mixing up the types
of caresses and areas being caressed
不同的爱抚和被抚摸的区域
(Woman) Mixing up the types
of caresses and areas being caressed
有助手保持皮肤的神经末梢反应
helps keep the skin's nerve endings
responsive.
有助手保持皮肤的神经末梢反应
helps keep the skin's nerve endings
responsive.
And there's no reason
you can't touch yourself
没有理由你不能爱抚自己
while your lover is touching you.
当你的爱侣抚摸你的时候
在你爱人面前正无拘无束的自慰
Being comfortable enough to masturbate
in front of your lover
在你爱人面前正无拘无束的自慰
Being comfortable enough to masturbate
in front of your lover
说明你信任他们 有助于他们了解
shows that you trust them
and helps them to get to know
说明你信任他们 有助于他们了解
the type of touch that
you most enjoy.
说明你信任他们 有助于他们了解
the type of touch that
you most enjoy.
你最喜欢的爱抚方式
the type of touch that
you most enjoy.
我们不应该认为爱抚只仅限于双手
(Man) There's no reason that touch
should be limited to your hands.
我们不应该认为爱抚只仅限于双手
The lips and teeth can deliver
exquisite sensations,
嘴唇和牙齿可以传递细腻的感觉
The lips and teeth can deliver
exquisite sensations,
帮助你的爱人爱慕她们的每一寸肌肤
helping your lover feel worshipped
on every inch of their body.
帮助你的爱人爱慕她们的每一寸肌肤
helping your lover feel worshipped
on every inch of their body.
Sensual kisses and
whispered sweet nothings
感性的吻 低声的甜言蜜语
will all add to the mood and
make you both desperate for more.
都会增加欲望 使你渴望得到更多
will all add to the mood and
make you both desperate for more.
爱抚伴侣是需要时间的
(Woman) Take time
when caressing a lover.
爱抚伴侣是需要时间的
(Woman) Take time
when caressing a lover.
给她们幻想下一步往哪抚摸的机会
Give them the chance for their mind
to imagine what's going to come next.
给她们幻想下一步往哪抚摸的机会
Give them the chance for their mind
to imagine what's going to come next.
一旦一个人的大脑受到刺激
Once someone's brain is stimulated,
身体就会紧跟大脑的意识
it's almost guaranteed
that the body will follow.
身体就会紧跟大脑的意识
it's almost guaranteed
that the body will follow.
女性特别中意缓慢的前戏
(Man) Women in particular
appreciate slow foreplay.
女性特别中意缓慢的前戏
(Man) Women in particular
appreciate slow foreplay.
尽管只有25％的女性可以达到高潮
While only 25% of women climax
from penetrative sex alone,
尽管只有25％的女性可以达到高潮
this figure increases to over 75%
这个数字会增加超过75%
if their partner spends
more than 20 minutes
这个数字会增加超过75%
if their partner spends
more than 20 minutes
只要她们的男人可以再持续20分钟
if their partner spends
more than 20 minutes
在爱抚和前戏方面
on touching
and other forms of foreplay.
在爱抚和前戏方面
on touching
and other forms of foreplay.
(Woman) Many people fantasize
when their lover is caressing them.
许多人幻想是爱人在爱抚她们
(Woman) Many people fantasize
when their lover is caressing them.
这完全是自然的健康的
This is entirely natural and healthy,
即使你不是幻想你的爱人
even if you are not fantasizing
about your lover.
即使你不是幻想你的爱人
even if you are not fantasizing
about your lover.
(Man) Communicating your desire
sexually with a partner,
与爱侣交流传递对性的渴望
无论是口头上的还是通过呻吟
或扭动身体的方式
whether verbally or through the way
you groan and move your body,
无论是口头上的还是通过呻吟
或扭动身体的方式
whether verbally or through the way
you groan and move your body,
是了解你在床上想要什么最简单的方法之一
is one of the easiest ways
to get what you want in bed.
是了解你在床上想要什么最简单的方法之一
is one of the easiest ways
to get what you want in bed.
And continue to communicate
whilst you are being pleasured.
当你正爽的时候也要继续交流
And continue to communicate
whilst you are being pleasured.
当你的情人爱抚你时
简单地呻吟表示你很享受
Simply moaning when your lover
caresses you in a way that you enjoy
当你的情人爱抚你时
简单地呻吟表示你很享受
and staying silent when they do
something that doesn't hit the spot
当他没做到位时保持安静
and staying silent when they do
something that doesn't hit the spot
will help them learn
what you most enjoy.
着将帮助他们了解你最喜欢什么
will help them learn
what you most enjoy.
(Woman) Most people simply
want their lover to be happy,
大多数人只是希望自己爱侣能够快乐
(Woman) Most people simply
want their lover to be happy,
如果你有信心问自己想要什么
and you will generally find if you have
the confidence to ask for what you want,
如果你有信心问自己想要什么
you will get what you need.
你将会得到你所需要的
爱抚自己和爱抚伴侣都很重要
(Woman) Touching yourself is
as important as touching a lover.
爱抚自己和爱抚伴侣都很重要
(Woman) Touching yourself is
as important as touching a lover.
直到你真正了解自己的身体
Until you truly know your own body,
you're unlikely to be able
to guide a partner
直到你真正了解自己的身体
you're unlikely to be able
to guide a partner
你不可能引导你的爱侣
如何满足你的欲望和自己的个人兴奋带
on how to satisfy your desires and
your own personal pleasure zones.
如何满足你的欲望和自己的个人兴奋带
on how to satisfy your desires and
your own personal pleasure zones.
虽然有些人鄙视自慰
(Man) While some people
stigmatize masturbation,
虽然有些人鄙视自慰
但它确实是完全正常的和健康的
it really is entirely normal and healthy.
玩弄自己的身体有助于建立自信
Playing with your own body
helps build confidence
玩弄自己的身体有助于建立自信
Playing with your own body
helps build confidence
了解自己的性反应
and teaches you about
your own sexual responses.
了解自己的性反应
and teaches you about
your own sexual responses.
(Woman) It's helpful to be aware
of your many erogenous zones,
了解自己许多的性感带 这是有帮助的
(Woman) It's helpful to be aware
of your many erogenous zones,
not just the genitals.
而非停留在肤浅的生殖器方面
每个人都不同
Everyone is different.
There is no right or wrong way
to stimulate yourself,
刺激自己的方式没有对与错之分
There is no right or wrong way
to stimulate yourself,
所以要去尝试不同的方法
so experiment with different methods.
(Man) Men have an arsenal of techniques
at their disposal.
男性储藏着他们所掌握的技巧
(Man) Men have an arsenal of techniques
at their disposal.
他们可以使用润滑油涂抹在手上
来摩擦和挤压阴茎和翠丸
They can use a lubed up hand
to rub and squeeze the penis and balls.
他们可以使用润滑油涂抹在手上
来摩擦和挤压阴茎和翠丸
They can use a lubed up hand
to rub and squeeze the penis and balls.
他们可以尝试不同的握住方式
They can experiment with different grips,
using one hand or both,
他们可以尝试不同的握住方式
They can experiment with different grips,
using one hand or both,
用一只手或双手同上
They can experiment with different grips,
using one hand or both,
甚至他们的阴茎摩擦其他东西
or even rub their penis
against something.
甚至他们的阴茎摩擦其他东西
or even rub their penis
against something.
Once you've explored your body alone,
一旦你独自探索你的身体
向你的爱侣展示你所掌握的技巧
show your partner what you've learnt.
自慰可以是最好的证明方式之一
Side by side, masturbation can be
one of the best ways to demonstrate
自慰可以是最好的证明方式之一
Side by side, masturbation can be
one of the best ways to demonstrate
引起伴侣对你的注意
what turns you on to your partner.
(Woman) When it comes
to pleasuring your man,
当涉及到取悦你的男人时
(Woman) When it comes
to pleasuring your man,
探索他阴茎的每一寸肌肤
explore every inch
of his penis and beyond,
探索他阴茎的每一寸肌肤
explore every inch
of his penis and beyond,
从他的翠丸抚摸到龟头
stroking him from his balls
to the tip of his shaft.
从他的翠丸抚摸到龟头
stroking him from his balls
to the tip of his shaft.
Follow his hands on how best
to stimulate his penis.
用手来刺激阴茎
Follow his hands on how best
to stimulate his penis.
If he is not fully erect,
如果还没有完全的挺直
那就紧握阴茎 温和用手给他噜管
grip the penis and gently pump it
with your hand.
那就紧握阴茎 温和用手给他噜管
grip the penis and gently pump it
with your hand.
你也许想让自己的双手涂有润滑剂
You may also want to coat your palm
with lubricant
你也许想让自己的双手涂有润滑剂
然后紧握他的阴茎上下来回的噜管
and then grasp his shaft and start
to move your hand up and down.
然后紧握他的阴茎上下来回的噜管
and then grasp his shaft and start
to move your hand up and down.
(Man) Experiment with
different techniques.
尝试不同的技巧
(Man) Experiment with
different techniques.
从龟头的正下方来握住阴茎
Try holding his shaft
right underneath the head
从龟头的正下方来握住阴茎
用拇指和食指来回的揉搓它
between thumb and finger
and rubbing it.
用拇指和食指来回的揉搓它
between thumb and finger
and rubbing it.
或者用涂抹了润滑油的手来紧握住
Or grasping the shaft firmly
in a lubricated hand,
或者用涂抹了润滑油的手来紧握住
拇指挑拨 双手上下来回的滑动
with your thumb on his fraenulum
and slide your hand up and down.
拇指挑拨 双手上下来回的滑动
with your thumb on his fraenulum
and slide your hand up and down.
Or use one hand to stroke his shaft
with smooth, even strokes
用一只手连续不断地抚摸他光滑的阴茎根部
Or use one hand to stroke his shaft
with smooth, even strokes
当另一只手绕着龟头做圆周运动时
while the other one moves around
the head in a circular motion.
当另一只手绕着龟头做圆周运动时
while the other one moves around
the head in a circular motion.
玩的时候注意情人的身体语言
(Woman) Watch your lover's
body language as you play,
玩的时候注意情人的身体语言
注意他是否喜欢你正在做的事
and check whether he likes what
you're doing as you go along.
注意他是否喜欢你正在做的事
and check whether he likes what
you're doing as you go along.
还有不要忽视了他们的翠丸
And don't ignore his balls.
可以随意挤压逗弄它们但要很温柔
Feel free to squeeze and tickle them,
but always be gentle,
可以随意挤压逗弄它们但要很温柔
因为揉搓翠丸是一个万无一失的方法
because a bruised testicle
is a sure-fire way
因为揉搓翠丸是一个万无一失的方法
让男性立刻找到那种感觉
to get a man immediately
out of the mood.
让男性立刻找到那种感觉
to get a man immediately
out of the mood.
一个男人接近高潮时
(Man) As a man nears orgasm,
他的翠丸会紧缩
你可以感觉到他的阴茎开始抽动
his balls will tighten and you'll feel
his penis start to pulse.
他的翠丸会紧缩
你可以感觉到他的阴茎开始抽动
his balls will tighten and you'll feel
his penis start to pulse.
有时也会很难感觉到
It'll also probably feel harder.
Maintain what you're doing
unless you want to extend the tease,
保持你正在进行的 除非你想延时挑逗
Maintain what you're doing
unless you want to extend the tease,
在这种情况下就要改变技巧
in which case change the technique.
(Woman) There's a lot to be learned
from watching your partner.
还有很多人是从看伴侣学习的
女性一般倾向去温柔地
Women generally tend
to prefer softer, slower
女性一般倾向去温柔地
Women generally tend
to prefer softer, slower
缓慢地
and more manual stimulation
than men.
缓慢地
and more manual stimulation
than men.
比男人更追求手的刺激
and more manual stimulation
than men.
观看她如何轻轻地摩擦阴蒂
Watch how she softly rubs
the shaft of the clitoris.
观看她如何轻轻地摩擦阴蒂
Watch how she softly rubs
the shaft of the clitoris.
直接挑拨阴蒂会使大多数女性感到不适
Going straight for the clitoral tip can
be uncomfortable for many women.
直接挑拨阴蒂会使大多数女性感到不适
Going straight for the clitoral tip can
be uncomfortable for many women.
观察她是如何因为激发而膨胀
坚持轻轻地给些压力
Look at how she swells with arousal
and keeps the pressure light.
观察她是如何因为激发而膨胀
坚持轻轻地给些压力
Look at how she swells with arousal
and keeps the pressure light.
女性更倾向于对男人温和的态度
(Man) Women tend to prefer
the gentler approach to men,
女性更倾向于对男人温和的态度
(Man) Women tend to prefer
the gentler approach to men,
所以注意她的手指如何在阴蒂抚摸
或拨弄她的阴唇
so notice how her fingers circle
around her clitoris or tease her labia,
所以注意她的手指如何在阴蒂抚摸
或拨弄她的阴唇
so notice how her fingers circle
around her clitoris or tease her labia,
而不是硬压或快速摩擦
rather than pressing hard
or rubbing fast.
而不是硬压或快速摩擦
当在你的爱侣面前自慰时
(Woman) When masturbating
in front of a partner,
当在你的爱侣面前自慰时
要诚实的对待就像你平时一个人的时候
be honest about what you really do
when you're alone.
要诚实的对待就像你平时一个人的时候
be honest about what you really do
when you're alone.
Although it can be tempting
to put on a graphic display,
虽然它可以生动地展示一种极强的诱惑力
尤其是如果你们常常一起看成人电影
particularly if you watch
a lot of adult films together,
尤其是如果你们常常一起看成人电影
particularly if you watch
a lot of adult films together,
没有一点持续的观察
there is no point going
for lots of penetration
没有一点持续的观察
and spreading of your labia
or finger licking,
没有一点持续的观察
and spreading of your labia
or finger licking,
用手指拨弄阴唇
如果你真正喜欢的是轻轻拨弄阴蒂
if what you really enjoy is
a light circling of your clitoris.
如果你真正喜欢的是轻轻拨弄阴蒂
if what you really enjoy is
a light circling of your clitoris.
你的伴侣只能学习自己在做什么
Your partner can only learn
from what you are doing,
你的伴侣只能学习自己在做什么
Your partner can only learn
from what you are doing,
如果你表现出你很享受
if you show what you genuinely enjoy.
这将是个好开头
如果他能看到你挥汗如雨的发挥
It'll be even more of a turn-on if he can
see you getting wetter as you play.
这将是个好开头
如果他能看到你挥汗如雨的发挥
It'll be even more of a turn-on if he can
see you getting wetter as you play.
女人比男人通常需要更长的时间才能达到高潮
(Man) It generally takes a woman
longer to climax than a man.
女人比男人通常需要更长的时间才能达到高潮
So, if you're going for a mutual
masturbation session,
那么要是你们彼此都自慰的话
有个好主意 有句格言女士优先
it's a good idea to apply the adage:
"ladies first".
有个好主意 有句格言女士优先
it's a good idea to apply the adage:
"ladies first".
这样的话都会满意
That way, you'll both be satisfied
感兴趣的是贯穿始终彼此在做什么
and interested in what each other
is doing throughout.
感兴趣的是贯穿始终彼此在做什么
and interested in what each other
is doing throughout.
Watching your lover masturbate
看着你的爱侣自慰
然后再加入进来帮助她达到性高潮
and then joining in
as she gets closer to orgasm,
然后再加入进来帮助她达到性高潮
and then joining in
as she gets closer to orgasm,
通过观察 使用各种你所学到的新技巧
using all the new tricks
you have learned from observing,
通过观察 使用各种你所学到的新技巧
using all the new tricks
you have learned from observing,
can be one of the sexiest show-and-tell
sessions you will ever experience.
你将经历最性感的表演
can be one of the sexiest show-and-tell
sessions you will ever experience.
(Man) It helps if you let your lover
show you by guiding your hand
这可以帮助你 要是你想通过手来向爱侣表达
(Man) It helps if you let your lover
show you by guiding your hand
如何做才是她最喜欢的刺激
how best she likes to be stimulated.
手指往里伸几英寸 感觉在G点的周围
Feel around her G-spot,
a few inches inside on the upper wall.
手指往里伸几英寸 感觉在G点的周围
Feel around her G-spot,
a few inches inside on the upper wall.
当这个地方有所充血膨胀时
你就知道你一定会找到它
You'll know when you've found it
when you find a area that swells
当这个地方有所充血膨胀时
你就知道你一定会找到它
轻轻地揉搓
when you stroke it
with a come-hither motion.
轻轻地揉搓
when you stroke it
with a come-hither motion.
G点的刺激是让女性可以射精的途径
(Woman) G-spot stimulation can be
the pathway to female ejaculation.
G点的刺激是让女性可以射精的途径
(Woman) G-spot stimulation can be
the pathway to female ejaculation.
(Man) Don't be afraid
to show your lover
大方的给你的爱侣展示
你是多么喜欢看她爱抚自己来自慰
how much you enjoy watching
her masturbate by touching yourself.
你是多么喜欢看她爱抚自己来自慰
how much you enjoy watching
her masturbate by touching yourself.
许多女性发现看她们的伴侣自慰
(Woman) And many women find
watching their partner masturbate
许多女性发现看她们的伴侣自慰
(Woman) And many women find
watching their partner masturbate
也会很兴奋这样可以促使她更接近她的性高潮
To be a turn-on too, so you may
spur her nearer to her orgasm.
也会很兴奋这样可以促使她更接近她的性高潮
To be a turn-on too, so you may
spur her nearer to her orgasm.
相反地大多数男性被激发出来
(Man) Conversely,
most men are aroused
相反地大多数男性被激发出来
by watching a woman lose herself
in sensual pleasure.
相反地大多数男性被激发出来
by watching a woman lose herself
in sensual pleasure.
通过观察一个女人失去自我的性快感
by watching a woman lose herself
in sensual pleasure.
不必害怕让你越来越兴奋的展示
So don't be afraid to let
your growing excitement show.
不必害怕让你越来越兴奋的展示
So don't be afraid to let
your growing excitement show.
它也很可能会让你的爱侣拚命想加入进来
It's more than likely to make your lover
desperately want to join in.
它也很可能会让你的爱侣拚命想加入进来
It's more than likely to make your lover
desperately want to join in.
(Woman) The man should add
more fingers
男性应该多运用手指
当他感觉爱人的欲望被唤起时
as he feels his lover
getting more aroused,
当他感觉爱人的欲望被唤起时
as he feels his lover
getting more aroused,
用他的另一只手抚摸她的阴蒂颈部或乳头
and use his other hand to caress
her clitoris, neck or nipples
用他的另一只手抚摸她的阴蒂颈部或乳头
and use his other hand to caress
her clitoris, neck or nipples
or to stroke himself.
或者抚摸自己
(Man) Frontage, or rubbing your genitals
against your partners,
互相摩擦彼此的生殖器
(Man) Frontage, or rubbing your genitals
against your partners,
可以达到妙不可言的刺激
can be a wonderfully stimulating twist
用较为传统的自慰方法
on more traditional methods
of masturbation.
用较为传统的自慰方法
on more traditional methods
of masturbation.
只要记住 你仍然需要使用避孕套
Just remember that you still
need to use a condom
只要记住 你仍然需要使用避孕套
除非你知道你是在安全期
unless you know you're safe
from STD's and pregnancy.
除非你知道你是在安全期
unless you know you're safe
from STD's and pregnancy.
当高潮来临时 要勇于表现出来
(Woman) When orgasm hits,
don't be afraid to let it show.
当高潮来临时 要勇于表现出来
(Woman) When orgasm hits,
don't be afraid to let it show.
Not only does it let your partner know
they should stop what they are doing,
它不仅让对方知道他们应该停止正在做的
Not only does it let your partner know
they should stop what they are doing,
还要尽量避免接触过度敏感部位
to avoid touching
over-sensitized areas,
还要尽量避免接触过度敏感部位
to avoid touching
over-sensitized areas,
it can also act as an incredible
turn-on for them,
对他们来说这也有可能是性高潮的假象
it can also act as an incredible
turn-on for them,
刺激使她们感觉好像是达到高潮
spurring them towards their own climax.
彼此自慰不仅仅是在前戏
(Man) Masturbating a partner
isn't just great foreplay,
彼此自慰不仅仅是在前戏
(Man) Masturbating a partner
isn't just great foreplay,
它可以有新的变化或者被一个奇妙的感官替代
it can make a refreshing change from,
or a wonderfully sensual alternative to,
它可以有新的变化或者被一个奇妙的感官替代
it can make a refreshing change from,
or a wonderfully sensual alternative to,
进行完整的性交
full-on sexual intercourse.
几乎所有在地球上的动物都使用舔来传达感情
(Man) Just about every animal on the
planet uses licking to convey affection.
几乎所有在地球上的动物都使用舔来传达感情
(Man) Just about every animal on the
planet uses licking to convey affection.
但是人类已达到一个全新的水平
But humans have taken it
to a whole new level.
但是人类已达到一个全新的水平
But humans have taken it
to a whole new level.
有多种方式当人们用他们的舌头来刺激爱侣
There are numerous ways in which
people use their tongue on a lover.
有多种方式当人们用他们的舌头来刺激爱侣
There are numerous ways in which
people use their tongue on a lover.
慢慢地舔直到舔遍爱侣的每一寸肌肤
Delicate licking, sensual lapping,
and tracing outlines on a lover's skin,
慢慢地舔直到舔遍爱侣的每一寸肌肤
都要照顾到
all have their place.
And licking isn't just reserved
for the most obvious body parts.
我们不仅要舔那些身体上明显的部位
And licking isn't just reserved
for the most obvious body parts.
Exploring your lover's
entire body with your tongue
用舌头探索你爱侣的整个身体
can make them tingle all over.
可以让她们全身酥麻
(Woman) Going from a standing start
straight to oral can be very sexy.
舌头也会使你感到性快感
(Woman) Going from a standing start
straight to oral can be very sexy.
但是如果你渴望爱侣用舌头
在自己最私密的地方游走
But if you make a lover crave your
tongue on their most intimate parts,
但是如果你渴望爱侣用舌头
在自己最私密的地方游走
她们渴望你所做的
they're more likely to be aroused and
eager when you finally get down there.
她们渴望你所做的
they're more likely to be aroused and
eager when you finally get down there.
(Man) The longer you extend the tease,
延长用舌头挑逗的时间
the more powerful a lover's
eventual orgasm is likely to be.
最终让爱侣速到高潮的最高点是有可能的
the more powerful a lover's
eventual orgasm is likely to be.
有可能是嘴 有可能是手指
达到全面爆发的性爱
Whether that happens with your mouth
or fingers or full-blown sex.
有可能是嘴 有可能是手指
达到全面爆发的性爱
Whether that happens with your mouth
or fingers or full-blown sex.
(Woman) Many women find oral sex
the easiest way to climax.
许多女性发现最简单达到高潮的方法就是口交
(Woman) Many women find oral sex
the easiest way to climax.
由于阴蒂的神经末梢比阴茎上的多
As the clitoris is much richer
in nerves than the penis,
由于阴蒂的神经末梢比阴茎上的多
As the clitoris is much richer
in nerves than the penis,
刚开始的吮吸并不难
start gently rather than sucking too hard.
你应该敏感感觉到
(Man) You should be
sensitive enough to feel
你应该敏感感觉到
(Man) You should be
sensitive enough to feel
她是否想要你舔得更快更猛
whether she wants your licks
stronger or faster.
她是否想要你舔得更快更猛
whether she wants your licks
stronger or faster.
即便对阴蒂进行简单的呼气
也会达到令人难以置信的刺激
Even simply breathing on the clitoris
can be incredibly arousing,
即便对阴蒂进行简单的呼气
也会达到令人难以置信的刺激
激发她的欲望 用嘴让她渴望更多
building her desire and making her ache
to feel your mouth around her.
激发她的欲望 用嘴让她渴望更多
building her desire and making her ache
to feel your mouth around her.
Try using the flat side of your tongue
rather than the tip
尝试用你的舌面 而不光是舌尖
Try using the flat side of your tongue
rather than the tip
一些女性更喜欢舔雪糕的方式
as some women prefer
a big ice-cream lick
一些女性更喜欢舔雪糕的方式
舌头在阴蒂的压力
to pressure of the point
of the tongue on the clitoris.
舌头在阴蒂的压力
to pressure of the point
of the tongue on the clitoris.
(Woman) The golden rule is not to see it
as a race to get her to a finishing line,
金色的原则是 她没结束时不要去看它
(Woman) The golden rule is not to see it
as a race to get her to a finishing line,
但可以让她沉浸在充满快乐感觉中失去自我
but to delight in losing yourself
in a joyous activity.
但可以让她沉浸在充满快乐感觉中失去自我
but to delight in losing yourself
in a joyous activity.
有些女性口交时会感到尴尬
Some women can feel self-conscious
about receiving oral sex,
有些女性口交时会感到尴尬
Some women can feel self-conscious
about receiving oral sex,
但如果你表示很乐意
but if you show that
you're not only willing
但如果你表示很乐意
but actively want to take your time,
并积极地为她服务
这会让她放心 当她嗅到品尝到不错的
it will reassure her that
she smells and tastes great,
这会让她放心 当她嗅到品尝到不错的
it will reassure her that
she smells and tastes great,
也能够放松的沉浸在自我享受中
and can relax into enjoying herself too.
放松可以给她带来美好的高潮
And with her relaxation
can come great orgasms.
放松可以给她带来美好的高潮
And with her relaxation
can come great orgasms.
(Man) As a woman nears orgasm,
her labia and clitoris will swell
当女人快到高潮时她的阴唇和阴蒂会膨胀充血
会变得湿润
and the wetness will increase.
At this point, you can add
a finger or two.
此时你就可以多放入一两个指头
At this point, you can add
a finger or two.
尝试用你的舌尖来进行更激烈的接触
Or try more intense contact
using the tip of your tongue.
尝试用你的舌尖来进行更激烈的接触
Or try more intense contact
using the tip of your tongue.
但同时要慢慢地来
But again, build up slowly,
否则她就会完全的失去那个时刻
as otherwise she may
lose the moment entirely-.
否则她就会完全的失去那个时刻
as otherwise she may
lose the moment entirely-.
口交应该如何开始
(Woman) Vary how you begin oral sex.
Putting your tongue on the shaft
of a hardening penis
用舌头刺激逐渐变硬的阴茎
通过诱惑的内衣秀来让阴蒂充血
or engorged clitoris through underwear
can be wildly erotic-.
通过诱惑的内衣秀来让阴蒂充血
or engorged clitoris through underwear
can be wildly erotic-.
Try lapping at the pubic mound,
the inner thighs, the balls,
可以尝试轻拍会阴部
Try lapping at the pubic mound,
the inner thighs, the balls,
大腿内侧
Try lapping at the pubic mound,
the inner thighs, the balls,
翠丸
Try lapping at the pubic mound,
the inner thighs, the balls,
时不时的让你的舌头游走于内衣之中
and occasionally let your tongue
snake inside the underwear-.
时不时的让你的舌头游走于内衣之中
and occasionally let your tongue
snake inside the underwear-.
虽然有许多口交技巧
(Man) While there are numerous
fellatio techniques,
虽然有许多口交技巧
they fall into two basic approaches.
但广泛的分为两种基本方法
For a slow and gentle tease,
or as a wonderful warm-up,
一种缓慢而温和的挑逗或者一个美妙的热身
For a slow and gentle tease,
or as a wonderful warm-up,
可以从翠丸到整根来舔阴茎
lick the length of the penis
from balls to shaft
可以从翠丸到整根来舔阴茎
lick the length of the penis
from balls to shaft
在你用舌头轻吻更敏感的龟头
before gently flicking your tongue
over the generally more sensitive head.
在你用舌头轻吻更敏感的龟头
before gently flicking your tongue
over the generally more sensitive head.
To extend the anticipation,
为了延长效果
迂回到阴茎根部的前列腺中
move back from his glands
to the base of his penis
迂回到阴茎根部的前列腺中
然后起到效果
and work your way up.
从一边到另一边或者到他的大腿内侧
Or from side to side,
or to his inner thighs,
从一边到另一边或者到他的大腿内侧
在移动之前
before moving back up.
(Woman) Try playing your hair
over his shaft
试着用头发刺激阴茎
(Woman) Try playing your hair
over his shaft
小心翼翼的舔食龟头
as you delicately lick the tip,
用嘴温柔的吮吸翠丸
softly sucking the skin between his balls
into your mouth.
用嘴温柔的吮吸翠丸
softly sucking the skin between his balls
into your mouth.
甚至可以把翠丸整个的吸进嘴里
Or even sucking his balls entirely
into your mouth.
甚至可以把翠丸整个的吸进嘴里
Or even sucking his balls entirely
into your mouth.
这一切都要小心
Do take it carefully though,
as the balls can be incredibly sensitive
这一切都要小心
Do take it carefully though,
as the balls can be incredibly sensitive
翠丸是相当敏感的
Do take it carefully though,
as the balls can be incredibly sensitive
并不是所有的男人喜欢这样做
and not all men like them
being played with.
并不是所有的男人喜欢这样做
and not all men like them
being played with.
或者更猛烈疯狂些
(Man) Alternatively,
or as things heat up,
或者更猛烈疯狂些
(Man) Alternatively,
or as things heat up,
更用力的吮吸
go for more intense sucking,
moving your head up and down,
更用力的吮吸
go for more intense sucking,
moving your head up and down,
上下来回移动你的头部
以至于他可以把阴茎全根投入你的嘴里
so that he can watch his penis
vanishing into your mouth.
以至于他可以把阴茎全根投入你的嘴里
so that he can watch his penis
vanishing into your mouth.
Many men find it extra hot
to make eye contact at this point,
许多男性发现在此时来个眼神的交流会更性感
Many men find it extra hot
to make eye contact at this point,
他可以发现你所做的是多么的爱他
so he can see how much
you love what you're doing.
他可以发现你所做的是多么的爱他
so he can see how much
you love what you're doing.
确保你的牙齿不要咬到嘴唇
(Woman) Make sure you keep
your teeth guarded behind your lips,
确保你的牙齿不要咬到嘴唇
不必担心进行的速度
and don't be afraid to set the pace.
要是他插入的太猛或是时机不对
If he thrusts too hard
or at the wrong moment,
要是他插入的太猛或是时机不对
就会立马做出反呕的反应
it can set off the gag reflex.
当你口交时要保持一只手握住阴茎
Keeping one hand on the penis
as you perform oral sex
当你口交时要保持一只手握住阴茎
这会有助于你控制节奏
will also help you stay in control.
What you are aiming for is creating
a warm, wet, tight combination
要让他紧紧地感觉到温暖湿润
What you are aiming for is creating
a warm, wet, tight combination
在你的阴道外面模仿他进入的感觉
that emulates the feeling of him
sliding in and out of your vagina.
在你的阴道外面模仿他进入的感觉
that emulates the feeling of him
sliding in and out of your vagina.
(Man) Masturbating the shaft or
softly tugging or cupping the balls,
自慰阴茎 温柔的拖拽 吮吸翠丸
用手指轻压他的会阴
or using your fingers to put
some pressure on his perineum,
用手指轻压他的会阴
or using your fingers to put
some pressure on his perineum,
在他翠丸和肛门之间的区域
that area between his balls and anus,
能使他更爽
can send him over the edge.
你可能想从他那儿得到允许
You may want to get an all-clear from
him
你可能想从他那儿得到允许
在你用手指刺激他的肛门之前
before you go sticking your finger
in his anus, however.
在你用手指刺激他的肛门之前
before you go sticking your finger
in his anus, however.
有的男人喜欢这样 但有些人却不喜欢这样
Some men love it, but others will
not take such an intrusion kindly.
有的男人喜欢这样 但有些人却不喜欢这样
Some men love it, but others will
not take such an intrusion kindly.
(Woman) If it's the taste of semen
that you really don't like,
如果你真的不喜欢精液的味道
当阴茎深喉时
take the penis at the back of your throat
绕过你舌头上大部分的味蕾
to bypass the majority
of your taste buds,
绕过你舌头上大部分的味蕾
to bypass the majority
of your taste buds,
and if you're squeamish
about swallowing,
要是你觉得咽下去是恶心的
那就让嘴离开阴茎
withdraw your mouth altogether,
and masturbate him to orgasm.
那就让嘴离开阴茎
给他自慰让他射精
and masturbate him to orgasm.
(Man) Different people prefer
different techniques,
不同的人喜欢不同的技巧
所以要解读爱侣的身体语言
so read your lover's body language.
要不耻下问
Don't be shy about asking questions,
even when you're in the middle
of pleasuring your partner.
要不耻下问
even when you're in the middle
of pleasuring your partner.
甚至了解她在做爱过程中的感受
even when you're in the middle
of pleasuring your partner.
毕竟要集中精神享受性快感
And, above all, focus on enjoying
the sensual pleasure
毕竟要集中精神享受性快感
of having your lover's most
intimate parts in your mouth.
毕竟要集中精神享受性快感
of having your lover's most
intimate parts in your mouth.
有些人可以接受口交
Some people get just as aroused
by giving oral sex as receiving it,
有些人可以接受口交
要是你头脑清醒的话
你也可能成为他们其中之一
and you may become one of them
if you get your mind into the right state.
要是你头脑清醒的话
你也可能成为他们其中之一
and you may become one of them
if you get your mind into the right state.
它真的可以让你充分的接受
It really can be every bit as good
to give as to receive.
它真的可以让你充分的接受
It really can be every bit as good
to give as to receive.
(Woman) Whilst straight-forward sex
is perfectly wonderful in itself,
尽管直接做爱是非常完美的
(Woman) Whilst straight-forward sex
is perfectly wonderful in itself,
但也有些人喜欢虐待或者恋物
many people also enjoy
some form of kink or fetish.
但也有些人喜欢虐待或者恋物
many people also enjoy
some form of kink or fetish.
对于这些人来说这不仅仅有裸露的刺激
For some, it may simply be
the exhibitionist thrill
对于这些人来说这不仅仅有裸露的刺激
看着爱侣跳脱衣舞或者自慰
of watching a lover
strip or masturbate.
看着爱侣跳脱衣舞或者自慰
of watching a lover
strip or masturbate.
Being able to observe a partner
in such an intimate way
这样能够用一个私密的方法来观察爱侣
了解她们所沉浸的来使你满足
and know that they're indulging
for your gratification
了解她们所沉浸的来使你满足
and know that they're indulging
for your gratification
传递强烈的性欲
can deliver an intense sexual charge.
其他人发现性感内衣
可以增加性生活中额外的快感
(Man) Others find that sexy lingerie
adds an extra frisson to sex
其他人发现性感内衣
可以增加性生活中额外的快感
that nothing else can match.
其他人发现性感内衣
可以增加性生活中额外的快感
that nothing else can match.
比起什么都没有
装扮和脱衣服的诱惑
Dressing up and undressing
for seduction
装扮和脱衣服的诱惑
can add a sense of naughtiness
and occasion,
装扮和脱衣服的诱惑
can add a sense of naughtiness
and occasion,
可以增加乐趣
can add a sense of naughtiness
and occasion,
特别是如果爱侣很欣赏这些尝试
particularly if a lover is
appreciative of the effort
特别是如果爱侣很欣赏这些尝试
要大方的赞赏
and lavishes you with compliments.
长袜和吊带是很受欢迎的
Stockings and suspenders are popular,
可以让长袜再暴露些
and giving a discreet flash
of stocking top
可以让长袜再暴露些
when you're getting out of a car
on the way to dinner
可以让长袜再暴露些
when you're getting out of a car
on the way to dinner
当你要下车去吃晚饭时
when you're getting out of a car
on the way to dinner
can make a man's mind
wander all night.
这样可以让男人彻夜为之痴狂
can make a man's mind
wander all night.
l慢慢地拉起丝袜
Even simply seeing a pair of stockings
being slowly unfurled up a leg
l慢慢地拉起丝袜
Even simply seeing a pair of stockings
being slowly unfurled up a leg
这样可以营造出足够欲望
can be enough to create
a spark of desire.
这样可以营造出足够欲望
can be enough to create
a spark of desire.
(Woman) And of course,
getting kinky isn't simply
当然变态的怪癖并不是简单的
(Woman) And of course,
getting kinky isn't simply
关于你穿衣和脱衣服的方式
about the way you dress or undress.
Spanking is one of the most
common fetishes,
拍打屁股是最常见的恋物行为
Spanking is one of the most
common fetishes,
常常是性爱的一部分
一方爱侣扮演主宰者的角色
often forming part of sex in which
one partner takes a dominant role,
常常是性爱的一部分
一方爱侣扮演主宰者的角色
另一方扮演服从者的角色
and the other a submissive one.
有了这个剧情双方都会被刺激
With this scenario, even something as
innocuous as tickling can be a turn-on.
有了这个剧情双方都会被刺激
With this scenario, even something as
innocuous as tickling can be a turn-on.
(Man) While most people seek out
the pleasure of touch,
虽然大多数人寻求爱抚的快感
疼痛的感觉也会释放出大量的内啡肤
the sensation of pain which also
releases a flood of feel-good endorphins
疼痛的感觉也会释放出大量的内啡肤
the sensation of pain which also
releases a flood of feel-good endorphins
让人十分亢奋
can be just as energizing.
这会被加重 要是拍打屁股开始很缓慢
This is exacerbated
if the spanking starts slowly
这会被加重 要是拍打屁股开始很缓慢
逐渐变得更加激烈
and gradually becomes more intense.
如果想持续更长时间
拍打屁股是可以到达效果的
(Woman) If a long, hardish
spanking is administered,
如果想持续更长时间
拍打屁股是可以到达效果的
(Woman) If a long, hardish
spanking is administered,
在这之后这是必要的安慰对你的爱侣来说
it is essential to comfort
your lover afterwards,
在这之后这是必要的安慰对你的爱侣来说
otherwise they may suffer a come-down
from their body's own natural high-.
在这之后这是必要的安慰对你的爱侣来说
otherwise they may suffer a come-down
from their body's own natural high-.
否则她们可能会遭受直上直下的打击
otherwise they may suffer a come-down
from their body's own natural high-.
快乐与痛苦可增加那些感觉
And teaming pleasure with pain
can really increase the sensations.
快乐与痛苦可增加那些感觉
And teaming pleasure with pain
can really increase the sensations.
(Man) Even if a kink
doesn't do it for you,
即使是你并不能做到的怪癖
(Man) Even if a kink
doesn't do it for you,
迁就你的爱人 你会发现自己
by indulging your lover,
you may well find yourself
迁就你的爱人 你会发现自己
使你们关系摩擦出前所未有的火花
bringing a previously unknown
spark into your relationship.
使你们关系摩擦出前所未有的火花
bringing a previously unknown
spark into your relationship.
恋物癖可以建立在深层的潜意识中
Fetishes can be based
deep in the subconscious,
恋物癖可以建立在深层的潜意识中
Fetishes can be based
deep in the subconscious,
连接你和你爱人的性心理
and connect you
to your lover's sexual psyche
连接你和你爱人的性心理
不存在没有恋物的性爱
in a way that non-kinky sex doesn't.
And you never know,
你永远也不知道
因为一个特殊的怪癖从来没有吸引过你
just because a particular kink or quirk
has never appealed to you,
因为一个特殊的怪癖从来没有吸引过你
just because a particular kink or quirk
has never appealed to you,
这并不意味着你不会喜欢它
要是你真的尝试过
it doesn't mean you won't enjoy it
if you actually try it.
这并不意味着你不会喜欢它
要是你真的尝试过
it doesn't mean you won't enjoy it
if you actually try it.
你可以到另一个层次
(Woman) You can take things
to another level
你可以到另一个层次
(Woman) You can take things
to another level
有角色扮演的怪癖
by bringing kinky role-play
into the occasion.
有角色扮演的怪癖
by bringing kinky role-play
into the occasion.
许多角色扮演的剧情包含一个权力游戏
Many role-play scenarios
involve a power play:
许多角色扮演的剧情包含一个权力游戏
Many role-play scenarios
involve a power play:
医生和护士 警卫和客人
doctors and nurses,
escorts and clients,
医生和护士 警卫和客人
骗子和处女
seducers and virgins.
你不需要穿着特别的装束
And you don't necessarily have
to dress up or use specialist props.
你不需要穿着特别的装束
And you don't necessarily have
to dress up or use specialist props.
只需要用性爱幻想来掌控着整个剧情
Simply using your imagination
can be all that's required
只需要用性爱幻想来掌控着整个剧情
Simply using your imagination
can be all that's required
假设把你送到城堡的地牢中
或者一个阿拉伯后宫
to transport you to a castle dungeon
or an Arabian harem.
假设把你送到城堡的地牢中
或者一个阿拉伯后宫
to transport you to a castle dungeon
or an Arabian harem.
(Man) Bondage, domination,
submission and masochism,
束缚 统治 服从和性虐待
统称为BDSIVI
collectively known as BDSM,
允许在关系中进行权力角色的探索
allow exploration of power roles
within relationships.
允许在关系中进行权力角色的探索
allow exploration of power roles
within relationships.
Some people get a thrill
out of relinquishing
一些人获得了快感
在卧室里玩束缚
or seizing control
in the bedroom,
在卧室里玩束缚
or seizing control
in the bedroom,
特别是如果这违背了他们在日常生活中的地位
particularly if this runs contrary
to their position in everyday life.
特别是如果这违背了他们在日常生活中的地位
particularly if this runs contrary
to their position in everyday life.
Household props can easily
be adapted to kinky purposes.
家用道具可以很容易地适应怪癖的目的
Household props can easily
be adapted to kinky purposes.
丝袜或丝巾可以成为束缚绳
Stockings or silk scarves
can become bondage ropes.
丝袜或丝巾可以成为束缚绳
Stockings or silk scarves
can become bondage ropes.
(Woman) By trying both dominant
and submissive roles with a lover,
通过双方努力与爱人扮演
占主导地位和顺从的角色
你会体验到前所未有的欲望
you may tap into previously
unacknowledged desires.
你会体验到前所未有的欲望
you may tap into previously
unacknowledged desires.
然而在开始任何性幻想和角色扮演之前
However, before engaging
in any fantasy or role-play,
然而在开始任何性幻想和角色扮演之前
However, before engaging
in any fantasy or role-play,
确保有明确的界限
make sure boundaries
are clearly defined.
确保有明确的界限
make sure boundaries
are clearly defined.
你在幻想中看到的可能在现实中过于极端
What may seem entertaining in fantasy
can be too extreme in reality,
你在幻想中看到的可能在现实中过于极端
What may seem entertaining in fantasy
can be too extreme in reality,
你认为你永远不会这样
and levels that you think
you'd never step beyond
你认为你永远不会这样
当你在亲热时会变得有点儿过
may become surpassable
when you're in the heat of the moment.
当你在亲热时会变得有点儿过
may become surpassable
when you're in the heat of the moment.
(Man) Before you start playing,
在你开始玩SM之前
要设定一个停止的词这是很有必要的
it's essential to set a safe word
which means stop
要设定一个停止的词这是很有必要的
and that your partner promises
faithfully to adhere to.
让你的爱侣忠实地遵守这个承诺
and that your partner promises
faithfully to adhere to.
许多人在角色扮演中喜欢使用
不要 停止 这些词语
Many people enjoy using the words
'no' or 'stop' as part of the role-play,
许多人在角色扮演中喜欢使用
不要 停止 这些词语
Many people enjoy using the words
'no' or 'stop' as part of the role-play,
所以选择了一个词语就像red
so choose a word such as 'red'
这是在性爱游戏中不太使用的词
which you are less likely to use
during the sex-play.
这是在性爱游戏中不太使用的词
which you are less likely to use
during the sex-play.
有些夫妇从电影杂志中
吸取灵感来发挥他们的幻想
(Woman) Some couples draw
inspiration for their fantasy play
有些夫妇从电影杂志中
吸取灵感来发挥他们的幻想
from X-rated material:
从来X级电影当中
从色情小说 色情杂志中
reading erotic stories,
looking at sexy magazines
从色情小说 色情杂志中
从成人电影中
and watching adult videos.
在日常生活中
大多数男性会看色情电影杂志小说
Most men have looked at some form
of pornography in their lives,
在日常生活中
大多数男性会看色情电影杂志小说
Most men have looked at some form
of pornography in their lives,
而女性的比例也在逐年增多
although figures for women
are on the increase too.
而女性的比例也在逐年增多
although figures for women
are on the increase too.
(Man) Producing home porn,
家用色情的生产
无论是图片的形式还是我们自己的视频
whether in the form of pictures
or videos of oneselfes,
无论是图片的形式还是我们自己的视频
whether in the form of pictures
or videos of oneselfes,
在这个数字时代都是很容易找到的
has seen a massive boost
in the digital age.
在这个数字时代都是很容易找到的
has seen a massive boost
in the digital age.
未经他人允许 千万不要去拍照和录像
While you should never take photos or
videos of anyone without their consent,
未经他人允许 千万不要去拍照和录像
While you should never take photos or
videos of anyone without their consent,
摄影师和模特在角色扮演中
是非常热的幻想角色
role-playing photographer and model
can be a hot fantasy.
摄影师和模特在角色扮演中
是非常热的幻想角色
role-playing photographer and model
can be a hot fantasy.
你事后可以随时删除任何图像
And you can always delete any images
you take afterwards.
你事后可以随时删除任何图像
And you can always delete any images
you take afterwards.
You may find it safest to ensure
that neither of you is identifiable
您可能会发现它是最安全的保证
无论你可以识别
You may find it safest to ensure
that neither of you is identifiable
在做任何家庭色情
in any home porn make,
should anyone find the footage.
在做任何家庭色情
in any home porn make,
should anyone find the footage.
任何人都可以找到镜头
in any home porn make,
should anyone find the footage.
除非你喜欢出风头
(Woman) Unless you're happy
to be exhibitionists,
除非你喜欢出风头
请确保你的脸在镜头之外
keep your faces out of shot,
and also ensure you hide
any unique piercings or tattoos
还要确保把你独特的穿孔或纹身隐藏起来
and also ensure you hide
any unique piercings or tattoos
坚持适当的保密你的身份
to keep your identity
properly protected.
坚持适当的保密你的身份
to keep your identity
properly protected.
如果你打算在线发布您的影片
That goes doubly so if you intend
to post your footage online,
如果你打算在线发布您的影片
在点击超高的的成人网站注册
on the user-generated adult websites
that are now in abundance.
在点击超高的的成人网站注册
on the user-generated adult websites
that are now in abundance.
(Man) Sometimes
a perfectly passable sex life
有时令人满意的性生活
(Man) Sometimes
a perfectly passable sex life
需要一些调整
好让它进入到令人亢奋的状态
just needs a little tweak to move it
into the mind-blowing category.
需要一些调整
好让它进入到令人亢奋的状态
just needs a little tweak to move it
into the mind-blowing category.
(Woman) In the end, good old
romance can often be best
最后美好的旧恋情往往是最好的
(Woman) In the end, good old
romance can often be best
维持关系中的情趣
for maintaining the spice
in a relationship.
维持关系中的情趣
for maintaining the spice
in a relationship.
爱慕和赞赏往往是生活中上等的春药
Affection and appreciation are often
the choicest aphrodisiacs in life.
爱慕和赞赏往往是生活中上等的春药
Affection and appreciation are often
the choicest aphrodisiacs in life.
性玩具已经有上千年的历史了
(Man) Sex toys have been around
for thousands of years.
性玩具已经有上千年的历史了
早期的假阳具被称为假阴茎
Early dildos, known as Olisbos,
were sold in Greece around 5,000 BC.
早期的假阳具被称为假阴茎
Early dildos, known as Olisbos,
were sold in Greece around 5,000 BC.
在公元前5000年的希腊就有出售
Early dildos, known as Olisbos,
were sold in Greece around 5,000 BC.
大约在同一时间
Around the same time,
Ben Wa balls,
大约在同一时间
Around the same time,
Ben Wa balls,
本华球
Around the same time,
Ben Wa balls,
还在被当做阴道润滑设备和刺激使用直至今天
still used as vaginal toning devices
and stimulators to this day,
还在被当做阴道润滑设备和刺激使用直至今天
still used as vaginal toning devices
and stimulators to this day,
were created in southeast Asia.
它起源于东南亚
(Woman) Olive oil was mentioned
as a sexual lubricant
橄榄油被提到作为性润滑剂
in texts dating back to 35080.
在公元前350年文本记载中
实际上虽然它不应该被用作润滑剂
Although it shouldn't actually
be used as a lubricant
实际上虽然它不应该被用作润滑剂
因为它会导致安全套的破裂
as it can cause condoms to break.
(Man) And cock rings, once made
from the dried eyelids of goats,
还有情趣环套是山羊的干眼皮
公元1200年记载被使用过
were used back in 1,200 AD.
到了公元1600年又有了象牙环套
By 1600, these evolved
into carved ivory rings,
到了公元1600年又有了象牙环套
By 1600, these evolved
into carved ivory rings,
一些钉子在性交被使用来刺激阴蒂
some with studs used to stimulate
the clitoris during intercourse.
一些钉子在性交被使用来刺激阴蒂
some with studs used to stimulate
the clitoris during intercourse.
(Woman) Vibrators were invented
in Victorian times
振动器在维多利亚时代被发明
(Woman) Vibrators were invented
in Victorian times
to provide orgasms as a medical cure
for hysteria or womb disease
提供作为歇斯底里或子宫疾病的医疗治愈高潮
在女性患者中
in female patients.
该工具是由医生管理的
The machines were administered
by doctors
该工具是由医生管理的
避免手腕疲劳
who previously had developed
tired wrists
避免手腕疲劳
who previously had developed
tired wrists
不必手动治愈这种歇斯底里
from having to cure
this hysteria manually.
不必手动治愈这种歇斯底里
from having to cure
this hysteria manually.
人们现如今性用品已不再忌讳
(Man) Nowadays sex toys
are no longer taboo.
人们现如今性用品已不再忌讳
(Man) Nowadays sex toys
are no longer taboo.
一个性用品商店你可以选购阴蒂跳蚤
At a sex emporium, you can pick up
clitoral stimulators, dildos and vibrators
一个性用品商店你可以选购阴蒂跳蚤
At a sex emporium, you can pick up
clitoral stimulators, dildos and vibrators
假阳具和振动棒
At a sex emporium, you can pick up
clitoral stimulators, dildos and vibrators
任何形状大小
of every shape and size.
The choice in men's toys has also grown
significantly over the last decade,
在过去的十年
选购假阳具等性用品也显著增加
The choice in men's toys has also grown
significantly over the last decade,
最引人注目的是自慰时代的到来
most notably with the arrival
of a masturbator
最引人注目的是自慰时代的到来
looking like an ordinary torch.
有的看上去就像巨大的火炬
(Woman) Around half of all women
in the West
在西方大约半数的女性
have a sex toy of some kind,
拥有性用具
她们中几乎有80％一起使用过
and almost 80% of them
use them within relationships.
她们中几乎有80％一起使用过
and almost 80% of them
use them within relationships.
You can use them to stimulate nipples,
a clitoris, vagina or anus,
你可以用它们来刺激乳头
You can use them to stimulate nipples,
a clitoris, vagina or anus,
阴道
You can use them to stimulate nipples,
a clitoris, vagina or anus,
阴蒂 肛门
You can use them to stimulate nipples,
a clitoris, vagina or anus,
或者阴茎
or indeed the penis, balls or prostate.
翠丸 前列腺
(Man) 80 don't see toys as something
purely to use on a woman.
所以不要认为这些玩具纯粹是女性使用的
(Man) 80 don't see toys as something
purely to use on a woman.
甚至有些性用品来自女性的设计
例如The Rabbit
Even toys such as the Rabbit,
designed with women in mind,
甚至有些性用品来自女性的设计
例如The Rabbit
can be used on the man.
也可以被男性使用
Try teaming it with oral
or manual stimulation.
尝试用嘴或手动来刺激它
Try teaming it with oral
or manual stimulation.
如果它没什么效果
If it doesn't float his boat,
you can simply put the toy aside.
如果它没什么效果
If it doesn't float his boat,
you can simply put the toy aside.
那你就简单地把玩具放到一边
If it doesn't float his boat,
you can simply put the toy aside.
要是它起了作用
If it works for him, you can both
enjoy more explosive climaxes.
要是它起了作用
If it works for him, you can both
enjoy more explosive climaxes.
你可以享受到更猛烈的高潮
If it works for him, you can both
enjoy more explosive climaxes.
女人往往比男人需要更多的刺激
(Woman) Women, though, often
need more stimulation than men
女人往往比男人需要更多的刺激
to attain orgasm,
来达到性高潮
每分钟6000下和可触摸的按钮
and what man is capable of 6,000 revs
per minute and at the touch of a button?
每分钟6000下和可触摸的按钮
and what man is capable of 6,000 revs
per minute and at the touch of a button?
许多女性定期使用性玩具
Many women who do use sex toys
on a regular basis
许多女性定期使用性玩具
更频繁的性高潮经验可以增加性爱信心
experience more frequent orgasms,
have increased sexual confidence
更频繁的性高潮经验可以增加性爱信心
和爱侣达到满足
and report greater satisfaction
with their partners.
和爱侣达到满足
and report greater satisfaction
with their partners.
这意味着在你们的关系中这并不是一个威胁
(Man) This means that rather than being
a threat to your relationship,
这意味着在你们的关系中这并不是一个威胁
(Man) This means that rather than being
a threat to your relationship,
vibrators and other sex toys
can be positively beneficial.
振动器和其他性玩具可给予积极有益的效果
vibrators and other sex toys
can be positively beneficial.
(Woman) When it comes
to introducing your partner
当涉及到给你伴侣介绍时
一起使用性玩具
to the concept of using
sex toys together,
一起使用性玩具
仔细的判断
judge it carefully.
有些夫妇可能开门见山的说
Some couples may be open enough
to say, "Fancy giving this a go?"
有些夫妇可能开门见山的说
Some couples may be open enough
to say, "Fancy giving this a go?"
让我们一起幻想
可能会吓到其他人
when others could be intimidated.
不久前一个女人使用一捆绑式的假阳具
(Man) Not so long ago, the idea
of a woman using a strap-on dildo
不久前一个女人使用一捆绑式的假阳具
to penetrate her male partner
would have been shocking.
不久前一个女人使用一捆绑式的假阳具
to penetrate her male partner
would have been shocking.
插入她的男性伴侣 这是让人震惊的
to penetrate her male partner
would have been shocking.
但是你现在可以买肛门性玩具
But now you can buy backdoor toys,
G-spot and prostate massage's
但是你现在可以买肛门性玩具
But now you can buy backdoor toys,
G-spot and prostate massage's
G点或者前列腺按摩器
帮助夫妇达到前所未有过的性快感
to help couples reach the parts
that never see the light of day.
帮助夫妇达到前所未有过的性快感
to help couples reach the parts
that never see the light of day.
今天的有些性玩具被设计成双向的
(Woman) Some toys nowadays
are designed for double penetration.
今天的有些性玩具被设计成双向的
(Woman) Some toys nowadays
are designed for double penetration.
有足够的前戏和大量的润滑油
With enough foreplay
and plenty of lube,
有足够的前戏和大量的润滑油
With enough foreplay
and plenty of lube,
它有惊人的乐趣 可以带来双重刺激
it's amazing the pleasures that
such double stimulation can bring.
它有惊人的乐趣 可以带来双重刺激
it's amazing the pleasures that
such double stimulation can bring.
这有额外的尺寸来增加性幻想
Then there's the extra dimension
of adding to sexual fantasy.
这有额外的尺寸来增加性幻想
Then there's the extra dimension
of adding to sexual fantasy.
你可以想象群交
You can imagine group sex
不用暴露自己 尝试它的风险
without exposing yourself to
the emotional risks of actually trying it.
不用暴露自己 尝试它的风险
without exposing yourself to
the emotional risks of actually trying it.
记住 关键词是玩
(Man) Remember, though,
the key word is 'play'.
记住 关键词是玩
那么无论你选择什么性玩具进入你的性生活
So, whatever toys you choose
to incorporate into your sex life,
那么无论你选择什么性玩具进入你的性生活
So, whatever toys you choose
to incorporate into your sex life,
确保最终的结果是令人愉快的
be sure that the end result is fun.
(Woman) Though many couples stick
to two or three favourite positions
虽然许多夫妇坚持最喜欢的两个或三个位置
throughout their lives,
在他们一生中
其实还是有几百个姿势
there are actually hundreds of positions
人们可以用它们来进行性交
that people can use
to have sexual intercourse.
人们可以用它们来进行性交
that people can use
to have sexual intercourse.
在互联网上你可以找到详细步骤的指南
On the internet, you can find
step-by-step guides
在互联网上你可以找到详细步骤的指南
On the internet, you can find
step-by-step guides
指导我们如何性交怎样从开始到结束
to doing everything from
the 'Pile-driver' to the 'Pinwheel'.
指导我们如何性交怎样从开始到结束
to doing everything from
the 'Pile-driver' to the 'Pinwheel'.
(Man) But there are really just
five main approaches to consider
但是有五个值得考虑的主要途径
在决定采用何种姿势来做
when deciding which way to do it.
Man on top.
男上女下式
女上男下式
Woman on top.
后入式
From behind.
盘坐式
Sitting.
站立式
And standing.
当然还可以考虑肛交
(Woman) Then there's always
anal sex to consider as well,
当然还可以考虑肛交
(Woman) Then there's always
anal sex to consider as well,
但我们都是晚些时候才会做
but we'll get to that later.
(Man) Man on top, also known
as the 'missionary position',
男上女下式也被称作传教士体位
(Man) Man on top, also known
as the 'missionary position',
通常被认为是过时的没激情的
is often considered
old-fashioned or dull.
通常被认为是过时的没激情的
is often considered
old-fashioned or dull.
但它实际上可以提高女性达到高潮的几率
But it actually offers a woman
a greater chance of orgasm
但它实际上可以提高女性达到高潮的几率
But it actually offers a woman
a greater chance of orgasm
因为这种姿势对阴蒂的刺激最大
because it allows for great
clitoral stimulation,
因为这种姿势对阴蒂的刺激最大
特别是你不用太着急
particularly if you don't rush it.
这种体位也有利于进行眼神的交流
This position is also conducive
to passionate eye contact
这种体位也有利于进行眼神的交流
This position is also conducive
to passionate eye contact
爱抚乳房 如果女人弯曲她的膝盖
breast fondling and,
if the woman bends her knees
爱抚乳房 如果女人弯曲她的膝盖
环绕她的伴侣的双腿
or wraps her legs around her partner,
可以更加深入和对G点的刺激
deeper penetration
and G-spot stimulation.
可以更加深入和对G点的刺激
deeper penetration
and G-spot stimulation.
女人也可以方便的爱抚男人的胸部和乳头
(Woman) The woman has easy access
to caress the man's chest and nipples,
女人也可以方便的爱抚男人的胸部和乳头
(Woman) The woman has easy access
to caress the man's chest and nipples,
这些也是他们的性感带
should they be an erogenous zone
for him.
这些也是他们的性感带
should they be an erogenous zone
for him.
她也可以紧握他的肩膀让指甲侵入他的背
She can also easily grip his shoulders
and rake her nails down his back,
她也可以紧握他的肩膀让指甲侵入他的背
She can also easily grip his shoulders
and rake her nails down his back,
当然还有无数的吻
and of course there's lots of scope
for both of you to kiss.
当然还有无数的吻
传教土体位是比较伟大的一种姿势
(Man) Missionary position
is a great starting-off point,
传教土体位是比较伟大的一种姿势
(Man) Missionary position
is a great starting-off point,
适合于感性和兽性的性行为
that lends itself to both
sensual and animalistic sex.
适合于感性和兽性的性行为
that lends itself to both
sensual and animalistic sex.
没有什么可以阻止你 无论是移动的频率
And there's nothing to stop you moving
from slow and teasing missionary
没有什么可以阻止你 无论是移动的频率
还是强度和速度
to hard and fast rutting in one session.
(Woman) Rotating the hips
in a figure of eight motion,
旋转臀部象数字8那样
moving your bodies
closer together or further away,
或远或近的移动你的身体
在传教士体位中也可以增加你自己的旋转
or adding your own unique twist
to missionary sex,
在传教士体位中也可以增加你自己的旋转
or adding your own unique twist
to missionary sex,
例如变化成老汉推车式
such as this reverse doggie,
会增加敏感度和深入的程度
can all increase sensitivity
and allow deeper penetration.
会增加敏感度和深入的程度
can all increase sensitivity
and allow deeper penetration.
还有一个原因 它是最流行的性交姿势之一
(Man) There's a reason it's one
of the most popular sexual positions
还有一个原因 它是最流行的性交姿势之一
男人和女人们都喜欢
with men and women alike.
(Woman) The next option to consider
is woman on top.
考虑女上位是下一个选择
(Woman) The next option to consider
is woman on top.
这个姿势可以让女性更自如的掌控
This position allows the woman
to be more in control
这个姿势可以让女性更自如的掌控
of the pace and power of thrusting
and the depth of penetration.
这个姿势可以让女性更自如的掌控
of the pace and power of thrusting
and the depth of penetration.
控制插入的频率 强度 深度
of the pace and power of thrusting
and the depth of penetration.
She can also be more in charge
of tending to the clitoris,
她还可以更好的掌控阴蒂的倾向
She can also be more in charge
of tending to the clitoris,
摩擦爱侣的耻骨
either by actively grinding it
against her partner's pubic bone,
摩擦爱侣的耻骨
either by actively grinding it
against her partner's pubic bone,
靠自己掌控
or by playing with it herself.
男人可以轻易地来回抚摸女人的乳房
The man has easy access
to the woman's breasts,
男人可以轻易地来回抚摸女人的乳房
The man has easy access
to the woman's breasts,
更容易接吻
and again, it's easy to kiss.
(Man) As with missionary,
there are myriad variations
正如传教士式还有无数的变化方式
of woman-on-top sex.
女上位姿势
It can be a seductive dance
这是诱人的跳动
with a woman grinding her hips
against her partner,
这是诱人的跳动
with a woman grinding her hips
against her partner,
女人和爱侣扭动着臀部
激情的对视碰撞出火花
looking into his eyes
as the pair rock to mutual bliss.
激情的对视碰撞出火花
looking into his eyes
as the pair rock to mutual bliss.
这是激情和主要的交流
Or it can be a passionate and dominant
exchange
这是激情和主要的交流
in which the woman hungrily
takes what she wants
女人如饥似渴地期盼着她所想要的东西
from a willingly supportive man.
从乐于给她这些的男人那里
女上位时女人可以做出诱人的扭动
(Woman) For an intriguing twist
on woman on top,
女上位时女人可以做出诱人的扭动
当男人坐在椅子上保待坐姿
there is always the seated position
with the man sitting on a chair
当男人坐在椅子上保待坐姿
或是在床的边缘
or on the edge of a bed,
with his partner straddling him.
或是在床的边缘
or on the edge of a bed,
with his partner straddling him.
爱侣可以跨骑在他身上
or on the edge of a bed,
with his partner straddling him.
(Man) This is a great option
这是很好的选择
要是你钟情于女上位可以相互亲近
if you prefer your woman-on-top
approach to be more mutual,
要是你钟情于女上位可以相互亲近
if you prefer your woman-on-top
approach to be more mutual,
这是容易的
男人可以简单的下降到女人的背部
as it's easier for the man to simply
drop the woman onto her back,
这是容易的
男人可以简单的下降到女人的背部
as it's easier for the man to simply
drop the woman onto her back,
让他成为整个过程的主宰者
should he decide he wants to take
a more dominant role in the proceedings.
让他成为整个过程的主宰者
should he decide he wants to take
a more dominant role in the proceedings.
(Woman) Woman-on-top sex
can be slow and tender
采用女上位可以时而温柔缓慢
时而猛烈快速
or hard and fast,
要是男人生殖器大的话这是最理想的姿势
and this is the ideal position
if a man is well-endowed,
要是男人生殖器大的话这是最理想的姿势
as it allows the woman to decide exactly
how much she is going to take
女人可以来决定插入的深浅
决定插入的力度
and how hard she is going to take it.
这是让男人更轻松的享受性爱的方式
(Man) It allows the man to enjoy sex
a more relaxed way,
这是让男人更轻松的享受性爱的方式
这些插入的力都来自大腿的肌肉
all that thrusting can be hell
on the thigh muscles,
这些插入的力都来自大腿的肌肉
all that thrusting can be hell
on the thigh muscles,
这允许他有足够的自由来向上插入
though it still allows him
enough freedom to thrust upwards
这允许他有足够的自由来向上插入
though it still allows him
enough freedom to thrust upwards
should he crave deeper penetration.
来达到他所渴望插入的深度
像传教土体位一样
(Woman) As with
the missionary position,
像传教土体位一样
女上位可以给阴蒂更多的刺激
woman-on-top gives
plenty of clitoral stimulation,
女上位可以给阴蒂更多的刺激
woman-on-top gives
plenty of clitoral stimulation,
相互达到高潮的理想姿势
making it a great position
for mutual orgasm.
相互达到高潮的理想姿势
making it a great position
for mutual orgasm.
(Man) Sex from behind,
or doggie style,
后入式或者老汉推车式
(Man) Sex from behind,
or doggie style,
可以插入的更深 对G点刺激更大
allows for the deepest penetration
and G-spot stimulation.
可以插入的更深 对G点刺激更大
allows for the deepest penetration
and G-spot stimulation.
男人可以轻松地接吻轻咬她的脖子和香肩
The man has easy access to kiss
and nibble the neck and shoulders,
男人可以轻松地接吻轻咬她的脖子和香肩
caress the back
or stroke the clitoris during sex.
抚摸背部揉搓阴蒂在整个性交过程中
caress the back
or stroke the clitoris during sex.
他可以抓她的乳房亲吻她的身体
He can cup the woman's breasts,
kiss her body,
他可以抓她的乳房亲吻她的身体
随意的享受他所钟情的
and generally lavish almost
every inch of her with affection.
随意的享受他所钟情的
and generally lavish almost
every inch of her with affection.
许多女性都喜欢老汉推车式
(Woman) Many woman
enjoy doggie style
许多女性都喜欢老汉推车式
(Woman) Many woman
enjoy doggie style
因为这种体位也适用于阴茎短小者
because it makes even
the smallest man feel larger,
因为这种体位也适用于阴茎短小者
because it makes even
the smallest man feel larger,
便于深入 可以插入的更深
and the woman can deepen
penetration even further
便于深入 可以插入的更深
通过给阴茎施压的办法
by pressing backwards
onto the man's penis.
通过给阴茎施压的办法
by pressing backwards
onto the man's penis.
尽管对于阴蒂亲密的接触这是不怎受欢迎的
(Man) Although it gets low scores
for intimacy and clitoral contact,
尽管对于阴蒂亲密的接触这是不怎受欢迎的
但老汉推车式在同性恋之间却很受欢迎
doggie style sex usually
receives high marks from guys
但老汉推车式在同性恋之间却很受欢迎
因为这种体位带有侵略性的插入
because it allows for aggressive
thrusting
因为这种体位带有侵略性的插入
让人有种原始野性的感觉
and it has a kind of raw
animalistic feel to it.
让人有种原始野性的感觉
and it has a kind of raw
animalistic feel to it.
但并不是只有后入式
(Woman) But there's no reason
that sex from behind
但并不是只有后入式
always has to have
the man in control.
但并不是只有后入式
always has to have
the man in control.
面对背的女上位可以让女性来控制速度
Reverse cowgirl
lets the woman set the pace,
面对背的女上位可以让女性来控制速度
Reverse cowgirl
lets the woman set the pace,
同时还可以让她方便地爱抚自己的阴蒂
whilst allowing her easy access
to caress her own clitoris,
同时还可以让她方便地爱抚自己的阴蒂
whilst allowing her easy access
to caress her own clitoris,
and gives the man a graphic view
that may well speed his climax.
给男性一个生动的感官享受快速的达到高潮
and gives the man a graphic view
that may well speed his climax.
(Man) At quite a wild end
of the scale can be standing sex,
野蛮的享受之后留下的伤痕这是正常的性爱
which can have a desperate
"must-have-you-now" urgency to it.
就像你现在必须要做的事
which can have a desperate
"must-have-you-now" urgency to it.
这对于那些早泄者是不错的选择
This makes it a great option
for quickies.
这对于那些早泄者是不错的选择
Whether it's from behind
or facing each other,
无论是从后面还是前面
Whether it's from behind
or facing each other,
站立式在做爱过程中可以提供必要的欲望
standing-up sex can offer a needy,
urgent compulsion to the act.
站立式在做爱过程中可以提供必要的欲望
standing-up sex can offer a needy,
urgent compulsion to the act.
很少以早泄的方式开始
(Woman) There are few sexier ways
to start an evening than with a quickie
很少以早泄的方式开始
(Woman) There are few sexier ways
to start an evening than with a quickie
once you're all dressed up
and ready for a night on the town
一旦你为了一整晚的狂欢都准备好了
once you're all dressed up
and ready for a night on the town
那你就可以开始了
when you really should be
on your way.
那你就可以开始了
when you really should be
on your way.
之后还有肛交
(Man) And then there's anal sex.
肛交已经从一个禁忌的行为
当时男人乞求他们的爱侣尝试
Anal sex has gone from being a taboo
act that men begged their partners to try,
肛交已经从一个禁忌的行为
当时男人乞求他们的爱侣尝试
到现在变得越来越流行
to becoming increasingly popular.
当然好的肛交
Of course, good anal sex,
meaning anal sex that
is pleasurable and painless,
当然好的肛交
meaning anal sex that
is pleasurable and painless,
意味着肛交是愉快并无痛的
meaning anal sex that
is pleasurable and painless,
而不是一两天的事
is not something
that happens overnight.
而不是一两天的事
It can take weeks or even months
for a partner to open up and relax.
这需要几周或者几个月的时间
来让她的括约肌放松
It can take weeks or even months
for a partner to open up and relax.
不要管姿势
(Woman) Regardless of position,
只要能让你们彼此都达到性高潮
ultimate sex is all about finding out
what works for both of you.
只要能让你们彼此都达到性高潮
不要害怕尝试
Don't be afraid to experiment,
and accept that making mistakes
and even laughing at various faux pas
知错就改 笑谈过失
and accept that making mistakes
and even laughing at various faux pas
are all part of the process.
都是过程的一部分
一起实践做爱 这充满了乐趣
Half the fun of learning about sex
together is the practice.
一起实践做爱 这充满了乐趣
Half the fun of learning about sex
together is the practice.
(Man) Sexual exploration
can be very exciting,
对性的探索是非常令人兴奋的
even without topping things off
with an orgasm.
即使性高潮过程中缺乏一流的技巧
even without topping things off
with an orgasm.
但是大多数人对于结果都不满意
But most people consider having
the big '0' as a solid finale to sex.
但是大多数人对于结果都不满意
But most people consider having
the big '0' as a solid finale to sex.
当然这种情况属于双方彼此的事
(Woman) Of course,
making that happen for both partners
当然这种情况属于双方彼此的事
(Woman) Of course,
making that happen for both partners
比听起来更难
can be more difficult than it sounds.
女性在性交时需要
更长的时间前戏和更大的刺激
Women who require more foreplay
and greater stimulation during sex
女性在性交时需要
更长的时间前戏和更大的刺激
Women who require more foreplay
and greater stimulation during sex
一般达到高潮有很多困难
generally have more trouble
reaching climax,
一般达到高潮有很多困难
generally have more trouble
reaching climax,
特别是在性交过程中
particularly via intercourse.
(Man) An erection is
psycho-physiological magic
勃起是要靠生理和心理共同作用
and can't always be relied on
to spring up on demand.
勃起是要靠生理和心理共同作用
and can't always be relied on
to spring up on demand.
而并非依靠突然的需求
and can't always be relied on
to spring up on demand.
女人不必责备男人或是自己
This is when the woman
should not blame him or herself,
女人不必责备男人或是自己
This is when the woman
should not blame him or herself,
but take charge.
但要负起责任
激吻
Kissing, caressing and talking sexily
can all help him firm things up.
激吻
Kissing, caressing and talking sexily
can all help him firm things up.
爱抚 谈性都有助于他快速硬起来
Kissing, caressing and talking sexily
can all help him firm things up.
或者你可以用嘴去刺激
Or you can use your mouth
more directly to spur things on.
或者你可以用嘴去刺激
Or you can use your mouth
more directly to spur things on.
而不是感到失措
And, rather than panicking,
男人应该有点儿性幻想
the man should think sexy thoughts,
幻想他正在独自享受狂欢
perhaps using the fantasies that
he revels in when he is alone.
幻想他正在独自享受狂欢
perhaps using the fantasies that
he revels in when he is alone.
他要坚信有许多种方法让爱侣得到满足
And he should remember there are
multiple ways to satisfy his lover
他要坚信有许多种方法让爱侣得到满足
And he should remember there are
multiple ways to satisfy his lover
even if his penis won't play.
即使他的阴茎不行
接受这些 因为它是正常做爱的一部分
(Woman) Accept this as a part
of normal lovemaking,
接受这些 因为它是正常做爱的一部分
(Woman) Accept this as a part
of normal lovemaking,
提供更好的口交机会
and an opportunity
for more oral pleasuring.
提供更好的口交机会
and an opportunity
for more oral pleasuring.
Stroking the perineum
or stimulating the prostate gland
抚摸会阴或者刺激前列腺
Stroking the perineum
or stimulating the prostate gland
如果这样做可以让他找到那时的感觉
if he's into that, can also bring things
back on track in record time.
如果这样做可以让他找到那时的感觉
if he's into that, can also bring things
back on track in record time.
如果这是一个涉及问题的避孕套
(Man) If it's a condom related issue,
then masturbating while wearing one
will help him get used to the sensation.
如果这是一个涉及问题的避孕套
then masturbating while wearing one
will help him get used to the sensation.
当手淫时戴上一个会有助于找对感觉
then masturbating while wearing one
will help him get used to the sensation.
Not having safe sex, though,
should not be an option,
没有安全的性行为
Not having safe sex, though,
should not be an option,
这不应该是一种选择
尤其是在这种关系的早期阶段
especially early in a relationship.
尽管需要许多努力才能得到
Yet, however much effort
it takes to get there,
尽管需要许多努力才能得到
但这美妙的结果还是值得的
the result should be
wonderfully worth it.
但这美妙的结果还是值得的
the result should be
wonderfully worth it.
(Woman) Female arousal is linked less
to direct sensory output from the genitals
女性的性快感需要直接的生殖器刺激
and more to relaxation
and lack of anxiety.
同时需要放松不要焦虑
and more to relaxation
and lack of anxiety.
扫瞄显示女性性高潮产生的活动
Scans show that female orgasm
produces activity
扫瞄显示女性性高潮产生的活动
来自所有用于处理情感的大脑区域
across all brain regions
that handle emotion.
来自所有用于处理情感的大脑区域
across all brain regions
that handle emotion.
Letting go of fear and anxiety
greatly increases the chance
放下恐惧和焦虑的机会大大增加
Letting go of fear and anxiety
greatly increases the chance
达到性高潮的几率
of reaching orgasm.
女性需要对自己的快乐负责
Females need to take charge
of their own pleasure.
女性需要对自己的快乐负责
Females need to take charge
of their own pleasure.
并不取决去于他是多优秀的伴侣
Don't be dependent
on how good a lover he is,
并不取决去于他是多优秀的伴侣
Don't be dependent
on how good a lover he is,
it's not his responsibility
to give you an orgasm -
让你达到高潮也不是他的责任
it's not his responsibility
to give you an orgasm -
you have to reach one for yourself.
你必须要靠自己达到
(Man) But a man can help enormously
by giving a woman time.
但是男性有助于给女性巨大的时间
(Man) But a man can help enormously
by giving a woman time.
在做爱前至少要保持20分钟的前戏
Engage in at least 20 minutes
of foreplay.
在做爱前至少要保持20分钟的前戏
Engage in at least 20 minutes
of foreplay.
As the American sex researcher,
Alfred Kinsey, showed,
正如美国性研究者阿尔弗烈德·金赛研究表明
over 90% of women will reach
their orgasm after this amount of time.
有超过90％的女性经过这段时间可以达到高潮
over 90% of women will reach
their orgasm after this amount of time.
第一次高潮要与后面的连续起来
(Woman) Link that with going
for your orgasm first,
第一次高潮要与后面的连续起来
(Woman) Link that with going
for your orgasm first,
让他用手 舌头或者振动器帮助你达到高潮
get him to help you reach one
with his hands, tongue or a vibrator.
让他用手 舌头或者振动器帮助你达到高潮
get him to help you reach one
with his hands, tongue or a vibrator.
女士优先的规则减轻你俩的压力
(Man) The "lady-comes-first" rule
takes the pressure off both of you.
女士优先的规则减轻你俩的压力
(Man) The "lady-comes-first" rule
takes the pressure off both of you.
(Woman) The two Fs
for a more guaranteed orgasm are:
为保证性高潮有两个因素
(Woman) The two Fs
for a more guaranteed orgasm are:
摩擦和幻想
Friction and Fantasy.
你拥有一个神奇的东西 而他们没有
You have a magic button
that he doesn't have.
你拥有一个神奇的东西 而他们没有
You have a magic button
that he doesn't have.
The majority of women,
when they masturbate,
大多数女性当她自慰时
The majority of women,
when they masturbate,
需要三至六分钟就可以达到高潮
take between three and six minutes
to climax,
需要三至六分钟就可以达到高潮
take between three and six minutes
to climax,
but it can take over 20 minutes with
their partner in penetrative intercourse,
而当她们和伴侣性交时 这就要超过20分钟
要是可以达到高潮的话
if it happens at all.
第二个因素是当你们做爱时要有性幻想
(Man) The second F is fantasize
while you're having sex.
第二个因素是当你们做爱时要有性幻想
(Man) The second F is fantasize
while you're having sex.
充分运用你的想象力
Let your imagination go wild.
The joy of fantasy is that
there are no rules or regulations.
可以随便的幻想
The joy of fantasy is that
there are no rules or regulations.
Bring in some of the thoughts you have
while you masturbate,
当你自慰时也可以去进行性幻想
let yourself visualize intensely.
可以自己沉浸在性幻想中
大脑是最强大的性器官
Your brain is the most powerful
sex organ,
大脑是最强大的性器官
Your brain is the most powerful
sex organ,
use it to help you reach your climax.
用它来帮助你达到高潮
当达到性高潮时 皮肤会变得更敏感
(Woman) During orgasm,
the skin becomes more sensitive,
当达到性高潮时 皮肤会变得更敏感
(Woman) During orgasm,
the skin becomes more sensitive,
因为身体需要更多的氧气从而加快呼吸
the body requires more oxygen
which speeds breathing,
因为身体需要更多的氧气从而加快呼吸
血压升高 面色红晕
blood pressure rises,
creating a pink flush in the cheeks,
血压升高 面色红晕
blood pressure rises,
creating a pink flush in the cheeks,
生殖器抽搐就像肌肉收缩
and the genitals pulse
as the muscles contract.
生殖器抽搐就像肌肉收缩
and the genitals pulse
as the muscles contract.
生殖器周围有许多神经末梢元
The genital region harbours
a multitude of different nerves.
生殖器周围有许多神经末梢元
The genital region harbours
a multitude of different nerves.
阴茎上就有6000多个
The penis has a total of 6,000,
而阴蒂上有8000多个
but the clitoris has 8,000 nerves.
高潮的感觉取决于这些地区的爱抚
The orgasmic sensation varies
depending on the area touched.
高潮的感觉取决于这些地区的爱抚
The orgasmic sensation varies
depending on the area touched.
有人说男性的高潮不同于女性
(Man) Some say a man's orgasm
differs from a woman's
有人说男性的高潮不同于女性
(Man) Some say a man's orgasm
differs from a woman's
还有的说阴道的高潮表现也不同于阴蒂的表现
or that a vaginal orgasm
differs from a clitoral one
还有的说阴道的高潮表现也不同于阴蒂的表现
因为它们有许多不同的神经元
because different sets
of nerves are involved.
因为它们有许多不同的神经元
because different sets
of nerves are involved.
The nerve that gives the orgasmic
feeling sends messages to the brain,
神经元给人的大脑发送性高潮的感觉消息
经过脊椎
bypassing the spinal column
这就是为什么瘫痪的人仍然有性感觉
which is what allows some paraplegic
people to still feel sexual sensation.
这就是为什么瘫痪的人仍然有性感觉
which is what allows some paraplegic
people to still feel sexual sensation.
神经元的集合叫做神经核
A collection of neurons
called the nucleus accumbens,
神经元的集合叫做神经核
口语叫做大脑的快乐中心
or colloquially
"the brain's pleasure center",
口语叫做大脑的快乐中心
变得异常活跃 作为女性性高潮的方法
becomes highly active
as a woman's orgasm approaches.
变得异常活跃 作为女性性高潮的方法
becomes highly active
as a woman's orgasm approaches.
大脑的一部分负责奖励和同情
(Woman) The part of the brain
responsible for reward and empathy
大脑的一部分负责奖励和同情
它进入高度戒备模式
goes into high-alert mode,
as does the one producing
the hormone oxytocin,
作为生产荷尔蒙的一种
as does the one producing
the hormone oxytocin,
亲密的化学物质
the bonding chemical.
这样就发生了性高潮
(Man) And so orgasm happens,
这似乎证明女性的性高潮明显长于男性
and it seems to last significantly longer
in women than in men.
这似乎证明女性的性高潮明显长于男性
and it seems to last significantly longer
in women than in men.
(Woman) When it comes to climaxing,
every couple is different.
每对夫妇的性高潮都是不同的
(Woman) When it comes to climaxing,
every couple is different.
You might enjoy mutual orgasms
quite often,
您可能会喜欢彼此经常达到高潮
You might enjoy mutual orgasms
quite often,
彼此之间产生效果 距离高潮不远
you may work each other up to a state
of near-climax with words alone,
彼此之间产生效果 距离高潮不远
you may work each other up to a state
of near-climax with words alone,
or it could take all night
and hours of foreplay.
或者它会伴随整完和前戏的几个小时
or it could take all night
and hours of foreplay.
你们双方可能会发现很难达到高潮
(Man) One or both of you may find it
hard to climax from sex alone
你们双方可能会发现很难达到高潮
(Man) One or both of you may find it
hard to climax from sex alone
这就需要手指 舌头 工具来帮助达到高潮
and need to reach conclusion with
the help of fingers, tongues or toys.
这就需要手指 舌头 工具来帮助达到高潮
and need to reach conclusion with
the help of fingers, tongues or toys.
只要你自己感觉不错
There is no right or wrong,
only what makes you both feel good.
只要你自己感觉不错
There is no right or wrong,
only what makes you both feel good.
就没有什么对与错
There is no right or wrong,
only what makes you both feel good.
这些事你只能一起来探索
And that's something you can
only discover together.
这些事你只能一起来探索
And that's something you can
only discover together.
尽管阴茎和阴道通常会引起注意
Although the penis and the vagina
usually get all the attention,
尽管阴茎和阴道通常会引起注意
Although the penis and the vagina
usually get all the attention,
但事实是你的嘴是任何性关系中最重要的部分
the truth is that your mouth is the most
important part of any sexual relationship.
但事实是你的嘴是任何性关系中最重要的部分
the truth is that your mouth is the most
important part of any sexual relationship.
嘴不只是接吻和口交
And not just for kissing and oral sex.
关键是用它来彼此交流分享
Using it for communication or sharing
is the big key
关键是用它来彼此交流分享
让你得到满足
towards getting your needs met.
关系加深 欲望就会改变
(Woman) As relationships deepen,
desires change.
关系加深 欲望就会改变
(Woman) As relationships deepen,
desires change.
人类进化和问题的产生
People evolve and issues arise.
随着坦率的交流 爱人们可以有效地解决
With open communication,
lovers can effectively address
随着坦率的交流 爱人们可以有效地解决
性伴侣中出现的所有问题
all the twists and turns
of a sexual partnership
性伴侣中出现的所有问题
all the twists and turns
of a sexual partnership
共同成长而非疏远彼此
and grow together
rather than drift apart.
共同成长而非疏远彼此
and grow together
rather than drift apart.
它可以通过所有的性行为
(Man) It is possible to go
through all the motions of sex
它可以通过所有的性行为
without allowing your emotions
to get too involved.
它可以通过所有的性行为
without allowing your emotions
to get too involved.
而不会让你被情绪化
without allowing your emotions
to get too involved.
But surely the best sex is the kind
that deepens intimacy and involvement.
但是当然最好的性行为是
一种亲密关系的深化与参与
But surely the best sex is the kind
that deepens intimacy and involvement.
对待一切要诚实 从你的性幻想
Being honest about everything,
from your erotic fantasies
对待一切要诚实 从你的性幻想
Being honest about everything,
from your erotic fantasies
到你终身的不安全感
to your life-long insecurities,
构建一种默契
builds the kind of rapport that
a quick one-nighter could never match.
构建一种默契
builds the kind of rapport that
a quick one-nighter could never match.
即使在这种关系的早期阶段
(Woman) Even in the early stages
of a relationship,
即使在这种关系的早期阶段
(Woman) Even in the early stages
of a relationship,
诚实会让你变得健康 也成为爱的纽带
honesty will help you develop
a healthy, loving bond.
诚实会让你变得健康 也成为爱的纽带
当事情没有按计划进行时
(Man) And when things
don't go as planned,
当事情没有按计划进行时
例如有阳痪的表现或者早泄的表现
or there's a droopy erection
or a just-out-reach orgasm,
例如有阳痪的表现或者早泄的表现
or there's a droopy erection
or a just-out-reach orgasm,
这是在谈论如何帮助你应对所遇到的尴尬
it's talking about it that's going
to help you survive the awkwardness
这是在谈论如何帮助你应对所遇到的尴尬
解决这些问题
and resolve the problem.
(Woman) A healthy sex life helps
produce a healthy psychological state.
健康的性生活有助于产生健康的心理状态
(Woman) A healthy sex life helps
produce a healthy psychological state.
除了伴随着一流的性高潮体验
Beyond the joys of having
first-rate orgasms,
除了伴随着一流的性高潮体验
Beyond the joys of having
first-rate orgasms,
在性爱期间所释放的荷尔蒙
the hormones that
get released during sex
在性爱期间所释放的荷尔蒙
the hormones that
get released during sex
可以培养幸福感
foster a sense of well-being
增加欲望 与躺在你身边的人结合在一起
and an increased desire to bond with
the person lying next to you in bed.
增加欲望 与躺在你身边的人结合在一起
and an increased desire to bond with
the person lying next to you in bed.
(Man) Sex offers the chance
to become
性爱提供了机会来适合
sexually, emotionally
and spiritually fulfilled,
性爱提供了机会来适合
sexually, emotionally
and spiritually fulfilled,
性
sexually, emotionally
and spiritually fulfilled,
情感和精神上的满足
sexually, emotionally
and spiritually fulfilled,
与另一个人共享亲密
and sharing intimacy with another
actually allows us
to better understand ourselves.
实际上可以使我们更好地了解自己
actually allows us
to better understand ourselves.
对于许多人忙碌的生活
(Woman) For many people
leading busy lives,
对于许多人忙碌的生活
(Woman) For many people
leading busy lives,
充实他们的性生活可能只是意味着
enriching their sex lives
might just mean
充实他们的性生活可能只是意味着
setting aside a few hours
with their partner
充实他们的性生活可能只是意味着
setting aside a few hours
with their partner
撇开自己的爱人几个小时
after the kids have gone to sleep,
等到孩子们部睡着了之后
早睡和被忽视的欲望死灰复燃
climbing into bed early
and rekindling neglected desires.
早睡和被忽视的欲望死灰复燃
climbing into bed early
and rekindling neglected desires.
(Man) As if the pleasures
of experiencing powerful orgasms
至于如果遇到强大的高潮乐趣
and a lover's blissful cries
weren't enough,
至于如果遇到强大的高潮乐趣
and a lover's blissful cries
weren't enough,
爱人幸福的叫声代表还要
and a lover's blissful cries
weren't enough,
good sex might actually help you
prolong your life
实际上质量好的性生活可能会帮你延年益寿
good sex might actually help you
prolong your life
和你所爱的人
and that of the person you love.
(Woman) With an incentive like that,
why would anyone resist the allure
伴随着这样的刺激为什么会有人抗拒诱惑
在他们的生活中
点燃欲望追求最大的性爱质量
of igniting desire and striving
for the greatest sex of their lives?
在他们的生活中
点燃欲望追求最大的性爱质量
of igniting desire and striving
for the greatest sex of their lives?